<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-06-05T10:49:30</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018173430</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018173430</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-01-04</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-05-22</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>sv</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-01-04</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Gemplus</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000159795396</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/173/018173430/000159795396.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бижута, които предават данни; Телекомуникационни апарати под формата на бижута; Умни пръстени; Преносими комуникационни устройства под формата на ръчен часовник; Електронно кодирани идентификационни ленти за китка; Смарт гривни; Банков софтуер.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Klenoty a bižuterie schopné datové komunikace; Telekomunikační přístroje v podobě šperků; Chytré prsteny (elektronická zařízení); Nositelná komunikační zařízení v podobě náramkových hodinek; Elektronicky kódované identifikační náramky; Chytré náramky; Bankovní software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Smykker som kommunikerer data; Telekommunikationsapparater i form af smykker; Smart rings; Wearable kommunikationsenheder i form af armbåndsure; Elektronisk kodede identitetsarmbånd; Smartarmbånd; Software til bankvirksomhed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schmuckwaren, die Daten übermitteln; Telekommunikationsgeräte in Form von Schmuckwaren; Smart-Ringe; Tragbare Kommunikationsgeräte in Form von Armbanduhren; Elektronisch kodierte Erkennungsarmbänder; Datenarmbänder; Banking-Software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κοσμήματα που κοινοποιούν δεδομένα· Συσκευές τηλεπικοινωνιών σε μορφή κοσμημάτων· Έξυπνα δαχτυλίδια· Συσκευές επικοινωνίας που προσαρτώνται στον χρήστη με τη μορφή ρολογιών χειρός· Ηλεκτρονικά κωδικοποιημένα περικάρπια αναγνώρισης ταυτότητας· Έξυπνα βραχιόλια· Τραπεζικό λογισμικό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Jewellery that communicates data; Telecommunication apparatus in the form of jewellery; Smart rings; Wearable communications devices in the form of wristwatches; Electronically encoded identity wristbands; Smart bracelets; Banking software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos de joyería que comunican datos; Aparatos de telecomunicaciones en forma de joyas; Anillos inteligentes; Dispositivos de comunicaciones que pueden llevarse puestos en forma de relojes de pulsera; Pulseras identificativas codificadas electrónicamente; Pulseras inteligentes; Software bancario.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Andmesidega ehted; Telekommunikatsiooniseadmed ehete kujul; Nutisõrmused; Käekelladena kantavad sideseadmed; Elektrooniliselt kodeeritud tuvastamise eesmärgil kasutatavad käepaelad; Nutikäevõrud; Pangandustarkvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Korut, jotka viestivät tietoja; Viestintälaitteet koruina; Älysormukset; Päälle puettavat viestintävälineet rannekellojen muodossa; Elektronisesti koodatut tunnistusrannekkeet; Älyrannekkeet; Pankkitoimintaan liittyvät ohjelmistot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bijoux permettant de communiquer des données; Appareils de télécommunication en forme de bijoux; Bagues intelligentes; Dispositifs de communications portables sous la forme de montres-bracelets; Bracelets d'identification à encodage électronique; Bracelets intelligents; Logiciels bancaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nakit kojim se mogu odašiljati podatci; Telekomunikacijski uređaji u obliku nakita; Pametni prsteni; Nosivi komunikacijski uređaji u obliku ručnih satova; Elektronički kodirane identifikacijske narukvice; Pametne narukvice; Bankarski softver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ékszer amely adatot kommunikál; Telekommunikációs készülékek ékszerek formájában; Okosgyűrűk; Hordható kommunikációs eszközök karórák formájában; Elektronikusan kódolt azonosító csuklópántok; Okoskarkötők; Banki szoftverek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli di gioielleria per la comunicazione di dati; Apparecchi di telecomunicazione sotto forma di gioielli; Anelli intelligenti; Dispositivi di comunicazione indossabili sotto forma di orologi da polso; Braccialetti d'identificazione codificati elettronicamente; Braccialetti intelligenti; Software bancari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Juvelyriniai dirbiniai, perduodantys duomenis; Juvelyrinių dirbinių formos telekomunikacijos aparatai; Išmanieji žiedai; Rankinių laikrodžių pavidalo nešiojamieji komunikacijos prietaisai; Elektroniniai koduotieji tapatybės atpažinties riešo raiščiai; Išmaniosios apyrankės; Bankinė programinė įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Juvelierizstrādājumi, kas veic datu saziņu; Telekomunikāciju iekārtas juvelierizstrādājumu formā; Viedie gredzeni; Nēsājamas komunikācijas ierīces rokas pulksteņu veidā; Elektroniski kodētas identifikācijas aproces; Viedās aproces; Banku programmatūra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġojjellerija li tikkomunika data; Apparat tat-telekomunikazzjoni fil-forma ta' ġojjellerija; Ċrieket smart; Tagħmir ta' komunikazzjonijiet li jintlibsu fil-forma ta' arloġġi ta' mal-polz; Brazzuletti tal-identita ċċifrati b'mod elettroniku; Brazzuletti intelliġenti (Smart bracelets); Softwer tas-servizzi bankarji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Juwelierswaren die gegevens overbrengen; Telecommunicatie-apparatuur in de vorm van juwelen; Smart rings; Draagbare communicatietoestellen in de vorm van polshorloges; Identiteitspolsbandjes (Elektronisch gecodeerde -); Smart armbanden; Banking software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Biżuteria przekazująca dane; Urządzenia telekomunikacyjne w postaci biżuterii; Inteligentne pierścionki; Urządzenia komunikacyjne do noszenia w postaci zegarków na rękę; Kodowane elektronicznie opaski identyfikacyjne na nadgarstek; Bransoletki inteligentne; Oprogramowanie dla bankowości.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Joalharia com funcionalidade de comunicação de dados; Dispositivos para telecomunicações em forma de joias; Anéis inteligentes; Dispositivos de comunicações portáteis sob a forma de relógios de pulso; Pulseiras de identificação codificadas eletronicamente; Pulseiras inteligentes; Software bancário.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bijuterii care comunică date; Aparate de telecomunicaţii în formă de bijuterii; Inele inteligente; Dispozitive de comunicaţii portabile, sub formă de ceasuri de mână; Brăţări de identificare codate electronic; Brăţări inteligente; Software bancar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Šperky, cez ktoré prebieha dátová komunikácia; Telekomunikačné prístroje v podobe šperkov; Smart prstene; Nositeľné komunikačné zariadenia v podobe náramkových hodiniek; Elektronicky kódované identifikačné náramky; Inteligentné náramky; Bankový softvér.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nakit, ki posreduje podatke; Telekomunikacijske naprave v obliki nakita; Pametni prstani; Nosljive komunikacijske naprave v obliki zapestne ure; Elektronsko kodirane identifikacijske zapestnice; Pametne zapestnice; Bančna programska oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Smycken som kommunicerar data; Telekommunikationsapparater i form av smycken; Smarta ringar; Bärbar kommunikationsutrustning i form av armbandsur; Elektroniskt kodade id-armband; Smarta armband; Programvara för bankverksamhet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>14</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Авторска бижутерия; Непарични монети; Идентификационни табели от благородни метали; Платинени часовници; Сребърни часовници; Часовници, изработени от матал, върху който е завалцовано тънко фолио злато; Ръчни часовници с телекомуникационни функции; Спортни часовници; Циферблати за ръчни часовници; Часовници; Автоматични часовници; Механични ръчни часовници; Електрически часовници; Електрически часовници; Коронки за ръчни часовници; Закопчалки за ръчни часовници; Часовници, изработени от злато; Часовници с вградени функции за запаметяване; Портмонета за ръчни часовници; Часовници на верижка (предназначени за медицински сестри); Ръчни часовници с емблеми; Части за часовникови механизми; Ръчни часовници с крачкомери; Емайлирани бижута; Емайлирани бижута; Бижута с изкуствени скъпоценни камъни; Нефрит [бижутерия]; Скъпоценни бижута; Емайлирани бижута; Златни нишки [бижутерия]; Медальони с капаче [бижутерия]; Пръстени [бижутерийни изделия]; Гривни [бижутерийни изделия]; Сребърни конци (бижутерийни изделия); Бижута, изработени от сребро; Бижута с вградини диаманти; Бижута, изработени от злато; Бижута от жълт кехлибар; Бижута, изработени от скъпоценни камъни; Бижута, изработени от сплави на благородни метали; Фирмени емблеми под формата на бижута; Предпазни верижки за бижута; Кутии за излагане на бижута; Бижута, съдържащи злато; Пръстени [бижутерийни изделия]; Посребрени пръстени; Златни пръстени; Поставки за пръстени от благороден метал; Захващащи цанги, които са част от бижута; Халки за ключове [халки за ключове с дребни украшения или декоративни накрайници]; Индентификационни гривни [бижутерия]; Часовници, изработени от златно покритие; Гривни; Дребни украшения за гривни; Посребрени гривни; Гривни [бижутерийни изделия]; Златни гривни; Позлатени гривни; Благотворителни гривни; Гривни; Гривни от благородни метали; Бижутерийни верижки, от благороден метал за гривни; Ръчни часовници, изработени от благородни метали или с тяхно покритие.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Osobní klenoty; Upomínkové mince; Identifikační destičky ze vzácných kovů; Platinové hodinky; Stříbrné hodinky; Hodinky vyrobené z válcovaného zlata; Hodinky se zabudovanou telekomunikační funkcí; Sportovní hodinky; Hodinkové ciferníky; Hodinky; Automatické hodinky; Mechanické náramkové hodinky; Elektrické hodiny a hodinky; Elektrické hodiny a hodinky; Natahovací korunky hodinek; Přezky na hodinky; Hodinky vyrobené ze zlata; Hodinky obsahující paměťovou funkci; Váčky na hodinky; Hodinky pro zdravotní sestry, ošetřovatelky; Hodinky s insigniemi; Součásti hodinových strojků; Náramkové hodinky s krokoměry; Šperky vyráběné technikou cloisonné; Šperky vyráběné technikou cloisonné; Skleněná bižutérie (imitace drahokamů); Jadeity (klenoty); Drahé klenoty; Smaltované klenoty; Zlaté nitě [šperky]; Medailónky [šperky]; Prsteny [šperky]; Náramky [šperky]; Stříbrné vlákno [stříbrné drátky]; Šperky vyrobené ze stříbra; Šperky obsahující diamanty; Zlaté klenoty; Šperky ze žlutého jantaru; Klenoty vyrobené z drahokamů; Klenotnické zboží vyrobené ze slitin drahých kovů; Šperky jako uznání pro spolupracovníky; Bezpečnostní řetízky (šperky); Kazety na šperky; Klenoty obsahující zlato; Prsteny [šperky]; Postříbřené prsteny; Zlaté prsteny; Držáky na prsteny ze drahého kovu; Lůžka prstenů jako části klenotů; Klíčenky (dělené kroužky s ozdobou nebo jako přívěsek); Identifikační náramky (klenoty); Pozlacené hodinky; Ozdobné kroužky a náramky; Přívěsky na náramky; Postříbřené náramky; Náramky [šperky]; Zlaté náramky; Pozlacené náramky; Charitativní náramky; Ozdobné kroužky a náramky; Náramky z drahých kovů; Řetízky z drahých kovů na náramky; Hodinky vyrobené ze vzácných kovů nebo jimi pokovované.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Smykker til personlig brug; Ikke-monetære mønter; Identitetsplader af ædle metaller; Platinure; Sølvure; Armbåndsure fremstillet af valset guld; Armbåndsure med indbygget telekommunikation; Sportsure; Urskiver til ure og armbåndsure; Armbåndsure; Automatiske ure; Mekaniske armbåndsure; Ure, elektriske; Ure, elektriske; Urkroner; Spænder til armbåndsure; Armbåndsure fremstillet af guld; Armbåndsure med en hukommelsesfunktion; Poser og etuier til ure; Armbåndsure til sygeplejere; Armbåndsure forsynet med insignier; Dele til urværker; Armbåndsure med skridttællere; Cloisonné smykker; Cloisonné smykker; Simili; Jade [smykker]; Ædle smykker; Emaljerede smykker; Guldtråd [smykker]; Medaljoner (smykker); Ringe (smykker); Armbånd (smykker); Spundet sølv [sølvtråd]; Smykker fremstillet af sølv; Juvelerarbejder med diamanter; Guldsmykker; Smykker af rav; Juvelerarbejder fremstillet af ædelstene; Juvelgenstande fremstillet af legeringer af ædle metaller; Smykkegenstande til at genkende virksomheder på; Sikkerhedskæder til smykker; Præsentationsæsker til smykker; Smykker indeholdende guld; Ringe (smykker); Sølvpletterede ringe; Ringe af guld (smykker); Ringholdere af ædle metaller; Kassefatninger som smykkedele; Nøgleringe [splitringe med vedhæng]; Navnearmbånd [smykker]; Armbåndsure fremstillet af pletteret guld; Armbånd; Charms (smykkevedhæng) til armbånd; Sølvpletterede armbånd; Armbånd (smykker); Guldarmbånd; Guldpletterede armbånd; Velgørenhedsarmbånd; Armbånd; Armbånd af ædle metaller; Smykkekæder af ædle metaller til armbånd; Armbåndsure fremstillet af ædelmetaller eller belagt hermed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schmuckwaren für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Münzen [nicht für Zahlungszwecke]; Namensschilder aus Edelmetall; Platinuhren; Silberuhren; Armbanduhren aus Walzgold; Armbanduhren mit integrierten Telekommunikationsfunktionen; Sportuhren; Zifferblätter für Armbanduhren; Armbanduhren; Automatische Armbanduhren; Mechanische Uhren; Elektrische Uhren; Elektrische Uhren; Uhrringe zum Einstellen der Uhrzeit; Klickverschlüsse für Armbanduhren; Armbanduhren aus Gold; Armbanduhren mit integrierter Speicherfunktion; Uhrbeutel; Schwesternuhren; Armbanduhren mit Insignien; Teile für Uhrwerke; Armbanduhren mit Schrittzählfunktionen; Cloisonné-Schmuckwaren; Cloisonné-Schmuckwaren; Strass [Edelsteinimitation]; Jade [Schmuck]; Wertvoller Schmuck; Emaillierte Schmuckwaren; Golddraht [Schmuck]; Medaillons [Schmuck]; Ringe [Schmuck]; Armbänder [Schmuck]; Silbergespinste; Juwelierwaren aus Silber; Mit Diamanten besetzte Juwelier- und Schmuckwaren; Goldschmuck; Bernsteinschmuck; Schmuckstücke aus Edelsteinen; Schmuckwaren aus Edelmetalllegierungen; Schmuckwaren als Anerkennung für Mitarbeiter; Sicherheitskettchen [Schmuckwaren]; Präsentationsschatullen für Schmuck; Juwelier- und Schmuckwaren aus Gold; Ringe [Schmuck]; Versilberte Ringe; Goldringe; Ringhalter aus Edelmetall [Juwelierwaren]; Fassungen als Teile für Juwelier- und Schmuckwaren; Schlüsselringe [Spaltringe mit Schmuckanhänger oder Zierrat]; Identifikationsarmbänder [Schmuckwaren]; Mit Gold plattierte Armbanduhren; Armbänder; Armbandanhänger; Versilberte Armbänder; Armbänder [Schmuck]; Goldarmbänder; Mit Gold plattierte Armbänder; Armbändchen [Schmuck] für wohltätige Zwecke; Armbänder; Armbänder aus Edelmetall; Schmuckketten aus Edelmetall für Armbänder; Armbanduhren aus Edelmetall oder damit plattiert.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ατομικά κοσμήματα· Νομίσματα μη ανταλλακτικής αξίας· Πλάκες ταυτότητας από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Ρολόγια από λευκόχρυσο· Ασημένια ρολόγια· Ρολόγια χειρός από λεπτά φύλλα χρυσού κράματος· Ρολόγια χειρός με ενσωματωμένη λειτουργία τηλεπικοινωνίας· Αθλητικά ρολόγια χειρός· Καντράν για ρολόγια χειρός και τσέπης· Ρολόγια χειρός· Αυτόματα ρολόγια χειρός ή τσέπης· Μηχανικά ρολόγια χειρός και τσέσπης· Ωρολόγια επιτραπέζια, τοίχου, χειρός και τσέπης,ηλεκτρικά· Ωρολόγια επιτραπέζια, τοίχου, χειρός και τσέπης,ηλεκτρικά· Στεφάνες για ρολόγια χειρός· Κουμπώματα ρολογιών χεριού· Ρολόγια χειρός από χρυσό· Ρολόγια χειρός με λειτουργία μνήμης· Μαλακές θήκες για ρολόγια χειρός· Ρολόγια χειρός για νοσοκόμες· Ρολόγια χειρός με διακριτικά σύμβολα· Μέρη ωρολογιακών μηχανισμών· Ρολόγια χειρός με βηματόμετρα· Κοσμήματα με διακόσμηση σμάλτου· Κοσμήματα με διακόσμηση σμάλτου· Στρας κοσμηματοποιίας· Νεφρίτης [κοσμήματα]· Πολύτιμα κοσμήματα· Σμαλτωμένα είδη χρυσοχοΐας· Κλωστές χρυσού [κοσμηματοποιία]· Μενταγιόν [κοσμήματα]· Δακτυλίδια [κοσμήματα]· Βραχιόλια [κοσμήματα]· Κλωστή από άργυρο (κοσμήματα)· Κοσμήματα κατασκευασμένα από ασήμι· Κοσμήματα με διαμάντια· Χρυσά κοσμήματα· Κοσμήματα από ήλεκτρον κίτρινο· Κοσμήματα από πολύτιμους λίθους· Κοσμήματα κατασκευασμένα από κράματα πολύτιμων μετάλλων· Κοσμήματα για την αναγνώριση του προσωπικού· Αλυσίδες ασφαλείας για κοσμήματα· Κουτιά παρουσίασης για κοσμήματα· Κοσμήματα με χρυσό· Δακτυλίδια [κοσμήματα]· Επαργυρωμένα δακτυλίδια· Δακτυλίδια από χρυσό· Θήκες για δαχτυλίδια από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Βάσεις δεσίματος πολύτιμου λίθου ως μέρη κοσμημάτων· Κλειδοθήκες [κρίκοι με κοσμημάτια ή διακοσμητικά αλυσιδάκια]· Βραχιόλια-ταυτότητες [κοσμήματα]· Επιχρυσωμένα ρολόγια χειρός· Βραχιόλια· Διακοσμητικά υλικά για βραχιόλια· Επαργυρωμένα βραχιόλια· Βραχιόλια [κοσμήματα]· Βραχιόλια από χρυσό· Επιχρυσωμένα βραχιόλια· Βραχιολάκια για φιλανθρωπική χρήση· Βραχιόλια· Βραχιόλια από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Αλυσίδες κοσμημάτων από πολύτιμα μέταλλα για περικάρπια· Ρολόγια χειρός από πολύτιμα μέταλλα ή επιστρωμένα με αυτά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Personal jewellery; Non-monetary coins; Identity plates of precious metal; Platinum watches; Silver watches; Watches made of rolled gold; Watches incorporating a telecommunication function; Sports watches; Watch dials; Wristwatches; Automatic watches; Mechanical watches; Clocks and watches, electric; Clocks and watches, electric; Watch crowns; Watch clasps; Watches made of gold; Watches incorporating a memory function; Watch pouches; Watches for nurses; Watches bearing insignia; Parts for clockworks; Wristwatches with pedometers; Cloisonné jewellery; Cloisonné jewellery; Paste jewellery [costume jewelry (Am.)]; Jade [jewellery]; Precious jewellery; Enamelled jewellery; Gold thread [jewellery]; Lockets [jewellery]; Rings [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Bracelets [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Spun silver [silver wire]; Jewellery made from silver; Jewellery incorporating diamonds; Gold jewellery; Jewellery of yellow amber; Jewellery made of precious stones; Articles of jewellery made of precious metal alloys; Corporate recognition jewelry; Jewelry guard chains; Presentation boxes for jewelry; Jewellery containing gold; Rings [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Silver-plated rings; Gold rings; Ring holders of precious metal; Collets being parts of jewellery; Key rings [split rings with trinket or decorative fob]; Identification bracelets [jewelry]; Watches made of plated gold; Bracelets; Bracelet charms; Silver-plated bracelets; Bracelets [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Gold bracelets; Gold plated bracelets; Charity bracelets; Bracelets; Bracelets of precious metal; Jewellery chain of precious metal for bracelets; Watches made of precious metals or coated therewith.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Joyería personal; Monedas que no sean pecuniarias; Placas de identidad de metales preciosos; Relojes de platino; Relojes de plata; Relojes chapados de oro; Relojes que incorporan una función de telecomunicación; Relojes deportivos; Biseles de reloj; Relojes de pulsera; Relojes automáticos; Relojes de pulsera mecánicos; Relojes eléctricos; Relojes eléctricos; Coronas de reloj; Cierres de relojes; Relojes de oro; Relojes que incorporan una función de memoria; Saquitos para relojes; Relojes para enfermeras; Relojes con insignias; Piezas de mecanismos de relojería; Relojes de pulsera con podómetro; Joyas de esmalte alveolado; Joyas de esmalte alveolado; Estrás; Joyería de jade; Joyas preciosas; Joyería esmaltada; Hilos de oro [joyería]; Medallones [joyería]; Anillos [joyería]; Pulseras [joyería]; Plata hilada; Joyería de plata; Joyería con diamantes; Joyería de oro; Joyas de ámbar amarillo; Joyería hecha de piedras preciosas; Artículos de joyería de aleaciones de metales preciosos; Joyería identificativa institucional; Cadenillas de seguridad para joyería; Cajas de presentación para joyas; Joyería que contiene oro; Anillos [joyería]; Anillos chapados en plata; Anillos de oro; Soportes de anillos de metales preciosos; Engastes que son partes de joyería; Llaveros [anillas partidas con dijes o abalorios]; Brazaletes de identificación [joyería]; Relojes de pulsera chapados en oro; Brazaletes y pulseras; Colgantes de pulsera; Pulseras chapadas en plata; Pulseras [joyería]; Pulseras de oro; Pulseras chapadas en oro; Pulseras con fines solidarios; Brazaletes y pulseras; Pulseras de metales preciosos; Cadenas de joyería de metales preciosos para pulseras; Relojes de pulsera de metales preciosos o chapados con los mismos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Isiklikud juveeltooted; Mündid (v.a rahalised); Isikuandmetega väärismetallist sildid; Plaatinakäekellad; Hõbekäekellad; Valtskullast käekellad; Sidefunktsiooniga käekellad; Spordikellad; Kellade numbrilauad; Käekellad, randmekellad; Automaatsed käekellad; Mehaanilised käekellad; Kellad (Elektrilised); Kellad (Elektrilised); Kellakroonid; Kellasulgurid; Kullast käekellad; Mälufunktsiooniga käekellad; Kellataskud; Meditsiiniõdede käekellad; Tunnusmärkidega tähistatud kellad; Kellamehhanismide osad; Sammuloenduritega käekellad; Cloisonné-tehnikas ehted; Cloisonné-tehnikas ehted; Strassist juveeltooted; Nefriit [juveeltoode]; Väärisehted; Emailitud väärisehted; Kuldniit [juveeltoode]; Medaljonid [juveeltooted]; Sõrmused [juveeltooted]; Käevõrud [juveeltooted]; Hõbelõng (hõbetraat); Hõbeehted; Teemante sisaldavad väärisehted; Kuldehted; Merevaigust juveeltooted; Vääriskividest valmistatud juveeltooted; Väärismetallide sulamitest valmistatud juveeltooted; Juveeltooted firmakingitustena; Ehete kaitseketid; Juveeltoodete esitluskarbid; Kulda sisaldavad juveeltooted; Sõrmused [juveeltooted]; Hõbetatud sõrmused; Kuldsõrmused; Väärismetallist sõrmusehoidikud; Metallvõrud (juveeltoodete osad); Ripatsitega võtmerõngad [võtmehoidjad]; Tunnuskäevõrud [juveeltooted]; Kullatud käekellad; Käe- ja jalavõrud; Käevõruripatsid; Hõbetatud käevõrud; Käevõrud [juveeltooted]; Kuldkäevõrud; Kullatud käevõrud; Käevõrud [heategevusliku otstarbega]; Käe- ja jalavõrud; Väärismetallist käevõrud; Väärismetallist ehteketid käevõrudele; Väärismetallist valmistatud või sellega kaetud käekellad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Henkilökohtaiset korut; Kolikot, jotka eivät ole rahoja; Jalometalliset tunnuslaatat; Platinakellot; Hopeaiset kellot; Valssatusta kullasta tehdyt rannekellot; Tietoliikennetoiminnon sisältävät rannekellot; Urheilurannekellot; Rannekellotaulut; Kellot; Automaattikellot; Mekaaniset rannekellot; Elektroniset kellot; Elektroniset kellot; Rannekellojen kuvut; Rannekellojen soljet; Kullasta tehdyt rannekellot; Muistitoiminnon sisältävät rannekellot; Rannekellojen pussit; Sairaanhoitajien kellot; Rannekellot, joissa on arvomerkkejä; Kellokoneistojen osat; Askelmittarilla varustetut rannekellot; Emalikorut (Cloisonné); Emalikorut (Cloisonné); Strassikorut; Jadekorut; Jalokivikorut; Emaloidut korut; Kultalanka [korut]; Medaljongit [koruina]; Sormukset [korut]; Rannerenkaat [korut]; Hopealangat [korut]; Hopeasta tehdyt korut; Timanttikorut; Kultakorut; Korut (Meripihka -); Jalokivistä tehdyt korut; Jalometallien seoksista valmistetut korut; Yritystunnistekorut; Korujen varmuusketjut; Korujen esittelylaatikot; Kultaa sisältävät korut; Sormukset [korut]; Hopeoidut sormukset; Kultasormukset; Jalometalliset sormustelineet; Holkkirenkaat korujen osina; Avainrenkaat [koristehelyillä tai avaimenperillä]; Tunnistusrannekkeet (korut); Kultapäällysteiset kellot; Rannerenkaat; Riipukset rannekoruihin; Hopeoidut rannekorut; Rannerenkaat [korut]; Kultaiset rannekorut; Kullatut rannerenkaat; Hyväntekeväisyysrannekkeet; Rannerenkaat; Jalometalliset ranneketjut; Jalometalliset koruketjut rannekoruja varten; Jalometalliset tai jalometallilla päällystetyt rannekellot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bijoux à titre personnel; Pièces autres que monnaie; Plaques d'identité en métaux précieux; Montres en platine; Montres en argent; Montres en or laminé; Montres avec fonction de télécommunication intégrée; Montres de sport; Cadrans de montres; Montres-bracelets; Montres automatiques; Montres mécaniques; Horloges électriques; Horloges électriques; Couronnes de montre; Fermoirs de montre; Montres en or; Montres avec fonction de mémoire; Pochettes pour montre; Montres infirmières; Montres avec insignes; Pièces de mouvements d'horlogerie; Montres-bracelets à podomètres; Bijoux en cloisonné; Bijoux en cloisonné; Strass; Bijoux en jade; Joaillerie précieuse; Bijoux en émail; Filés d'or [bijouterie]; Médaillons [bijouterie]; Bagues [bijouterie]; Bracelets [bijouterie]; Argent filé; Bijoux en argent; Bijoux avec diamants; Bijoux en or; Bijoux d'ambre jaune; Bijoux en pierres précieuses; Articles de bijouterie-joaillerie en alliages de métaux précieux; Bijoux à identifiant institutionnel; Chaînettes de sécurité pour bijoux; Coffrets-présentoirs à bijoux; Bijoux contenant de l'or; Bagues [bijouterie]; Bagues en plaqué argent; Bagues en or; Baguiers en métaux précieux [présentoirs]; Chatons, à savoir pièces de bijoux; Porte-clés [anneaux brisés avec breloque ou colifichet]; Bracelets d'identification [bijouterie]; Montres en plaqué or; Bracelets; Breloques (bijouterie); Bracelets en plaqué argent; Bracelets [bijouterie]; Bracelets en or; Bracelets plaqués or; Bracelets pour œuvres de charité; Bracelets; Bracelets en métaux précieux; Chaînes de bijouterie en métaux précieux pour bracelets; Montres en métaux précieux ou plaqués de métaux précieux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Osobni nakit; Nemonetarne kovanice; Identifikacijske pločice od plemenitih metala; Satovi od platine; Srebrni satovi; Ručni satovi od valjanog zlata; Ručni satovi s telekomunikacijskom funkcijom; Sportski satovi; Brojčanici za ručne satove; Ručni satovi; Automatski satovi; Mehanički satovi; Električni zidni, stolni i ručni satovi; Električni zidni, stolni i ručni satovi; Zupčanici za satove; Kopče za satove; Ručni satovi od zlata; Ručni satovi s memorijskom funkcijom; Torbice za satove; Ručni satovi za medicinske sestre; Ručni satovi sa znakovljem; Dijelovi sata; Ručni satovi s pedometrima; Cloisonne nakit; Cloisonne nakit; Bižuterija; Žad [nakit]; Dragocjen nakit; Emajlirani nakit; Zlatne niti [nakit]; Medaljoni [nakit]; Prstenje [nakit]; Narukvice [nakit]; Srebrna nit; Nakit napravljen od srebra; Nakit s ugrađenim dijamantima; Zlatni nakit; Nakit od jantara; Nakit napravljen od dragog kamenja; Nakit od legura plemenitih metala; Nakit koji se daruje zaposlenicima za postignuća; Sigurnosni lančići za nakit; Kutije za izlaganje nakita; Nakit koji sadržava zlato; Prstenje [nakit]; Posrebreni prsteni; Zlatno prstenje; Držači prstenja od plemenitih metala; Ležišta kao dijelovi nakita; Privjesci za ključeve [alke s drangulijama ili ukrasnim privjescima]; Identifikacijske narukvice [nakit]; Pozlaćeni ručni satovi; Narukvice; Privjesci za narukvice; Posrebrene narukvice; Narukvice [nakit]; Zlatne narukvice; Pozlaćene narukvice; Narukvice za dobrotvorne svrhe; Narukvice; Narukvice od plemenitih metala; Lančić od plemenitog metala za narukvice; Satovi od plemenitih metala ili njima obloženi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egyedi tervezésű ékszerek; Érmék, pénzérmék [nem fizetőeszköz]; Nemesfémből készült azonosító táblák; Platina karórák; Ezüst karórák; Hengerelt aranyból készült karórák; Telekommunikációs funkciót tartalmazó karórák; Sportórák; Karóralapok; Órák; Automata karórák; Mechanikus órák; Elektronikus órák, karórák; Elektronikus órák, karórák; Óra felhúzókoronák; Óraszíj kapcsok; Aranyból készült karórák; Memóriafunkciót tartalmazó karórák; Óratartó tasakok; Órák nővéreknek; Jelzéssel ellátott karórák; Óraszerkezetek részei; Lépésszámlálóval rendelkező karórák; Zománcozott ékszerek; Zománcozott ékszerek; Strassz [drágakő utánzat]; Jáde ékszerek; Ékszerek nemes anyagokból; Zománc ékszerek; Aranyszál [ékszerekhez]; Medálok [ékszerek]; Gyűrűk [ékszerek]; Karkötők [ékszerek]; Ezüstcérna; Ezüst ékszerek; Gyémántot tartalmazó ékszerek; Arany ékszerek; Ékszerek borostyánkőből; Drágakövekből készült ékszerek; Nemesfém ötvözetekből készült ékszerek; Munkahelyi elismerést jelképező ékszerek; Ékszer biztonsági láncok; Ékszerbemutató dobozok; Aranytartalmú ékszerek; Gyűrűk [ékszerek]; Ezüsttel futtatott gyűrűk; Aranygyűrűk; Nemesfém gyűrűtartók; Ékszerek részét képező kőfoglalatok; Kulcskarikák [apró díszekkel, fityegőkkel]; Azonosító karkötők [ékszerek]; Futtatott aranyból készült karórák; Karperecek és karkötők; Karkötőre fűzhető díszek; Ezüsttel futtatott karkötők; Karkötők [ékszerek]; Arany karkötők; Aranyozott karkötők; Jótékonysági karkötők; Karperecek és karkötők; Nemesfémből készült karkötők, karperecek; Nemesfém ékszerláncok karkötőkhöz; Nemesfémből készült vagy azzal bevont karórák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli di gioielleria personale; Monete non in corso; Targhe d'identificazione in metallo prezioso; Orologi di platino; Orologi d'argento; Orologi in oro laminato; Orologi con funzione di telecomunicazione; Orologi sportivi; Quadranti per orologi; Orologi da polso; Orologi automatici; Orologi meccanici; Orologi elettrici; Orologi elettrici; Lunette per orologi; Chiusure per orologi; Orologi in oro; Orologi con funzioni di memoria; Borsellini per orologi; Orologi per infermieri; Orologi contenenti decorazioni; Pezzi per meccanismi di orologeria; Orologi da polso con contapassi; Gioielli cloisonné; Gioielli cloisonné; Bigiotteria; Articoli di gioielleria in giada; Gioielleria preziosa; Gioielli smaltati; Filati d'oro [gioielleria]; Medaglioni [gioielleria]; Anelli [gioielleria]; Braccialetti [gioielleria]; Argento filato; Articoli di gioielleria in argento; Articoli di gioielleria comprendenti diamanti; Gioielleria in oro; Gioielli di ambra gialla; Articoli di gioielleria in pietre preziose; Articoli di gioielleria in leghe di metalli preziosi; Goielleria per riconoscimenti aziendali; Catenine di sicurezza per gioielleria; Astucci di presentazione di gioielli; Articoli di gioielleria contenenti oro; Anelli [gioielleria]; Anelli placcati in argento; Anelli in oro; Porta anelli in metallo prezioso; Castoni ovvero parti di gioielleria; Portachiavi [anelli portachiavi con gingillo o charm]; Braccialetti d'identificazione [gioielleria]; Orologi in oro placcato; Braccialetti; Ciondoli per braccialetti; Braccialetti placcati in argento; Braccialetti [gioielleria]; Braccialetti d'oro; Braccialetti placcati oro; Braccialetti per beneficienza; Braccialetti; Braccialetti in metalli preziosi; Catenelle in metalli preziosi per braccialetti; Orologi in metalli preziosi o placcati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Juvelyriniai dirbiniai (asmeniniai); Nepiniginės monetos; Identifikavimo plokštės iš brangiųjų metalų; Platininiai laikrodžiai; Sidabriniai laikrodžiai; Lakštinio aukso laikrodžiai; Laikrodžiai su telekomunikacijos funkcija; Laikrodžiai (sporto); Rankinių laikrodžių ciferblatai; Laikrodžiai [kišeniniai, rankiniai]; Automatiniai rankiniai laikrodžiai; Mechaniniai laikrodžiai; Laikrodžiai (elektriniai); Laikrodžiai (elektriniai); Laikrodžio karūnėlės; Laikrodžių sąsagos; Auksiniai laikrodžiai; Laikrodžiai su atminties funkcija; Maišeliai laikrodžiui įdėti; Rankiniai slaugytojų laikrodžiai; Laikrodžiai su skiriamaisiais ženklais; Laikrodinių mechanizmų dalys; Rankiniai laikrodžiai su žingsniamačiais; Kluazonė juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Kluazonė juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Strazai; Nefritas [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Didelės vertės juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Emaliuoti juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Auksasiūliai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Medalionai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Žiedai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Apyrankės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Sidabro verpalai; Juvelyriniai dirbiniai, pagaminti iš sidabro; Papuošalai su inkrustuotais deimantais; Auksiniai juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Gintaro juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Brangakmenių juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Juvelyriniai dirbiniai, pagaminti iš brangiųjų metalų lydinių; Įmonių apdovanojimai už nuopelnus (papuošalai); Papuošalų apsaugos grandinėlės; Juvelyrinių dirbinių dovanų dėžutės; Juvelyriniai dirbiniai, kurių sudėtyje yra aukso; Žiedai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Sidabruoti žiedai; Auksiniai žiedai; Žiedų laikikliai iš brangiųjų metalų; Aptaisai [juvelyrinių dirbinių dalys]; Raktų žiedai [su pakabučiais]; Identifikavimo apyrankės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Laikrodžiai [dengti auksu]; Apyrankės; Apyrankių karuliai; Sidabruotos apyrankės; Apyrankės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Auksinės apyrankės; Paauksuotos apyrankės; Labdaros apyrankės; Apyrankės; Apyrankės iš brangiųjų metalų; Apyrankių brangiųjų metalų grandinėlės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Brangiųjų metalų arba jais padengti rankiniai laikrodžiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Individuālie juvelierizstrādājumi; Nemonetāras monētas; No dārgmetāla gatavotas identitātes plāksnītes; Platīna rokas pulksteņi; Sudraba rokas pulksteņi; Apzeltīti rokas pulksteņi; Rokas pulksteņi ar telekomunikāciju funkciju; Sporta pulksteņi; Rokas un kabatas pulksteņu ciparnīcas; Rokas pulksteņi; Automātiskie rokas pulksteņi; Mehāniskie pulksteņi; Elektriskie pulksteņi un rokas pulksteņi; Elektriskie pulksteņi un rokas pulksteņi; Pulksteņu regulētājgalviņas; Rokas pulksteņu sprādzes; Rokas un kabatas pulksteņi no zelta; Rokas pulksteņi ar atmiņas funkciju; Rokas vai kabatas pulksteņu maciņi; Medmāsu pulksteņi; Pulksteņi ar goda zīmēm; Pulksteņu mehānismu daļas; Rokaspulksteņi ar pedometriem; Kluazonē [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Kluazonē [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Strass [stikla juvelierizstrādājumi]; Nefrīta juvelierizstrādājumi; Dārglietas juvelierizstrādājumu veidā; Emaljētas rotaslietas; Zelta diegi (juvelierizstrādājumi); Medaljoni [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Gredzeni (juvelierizstrādājumi); Rokassprādzes (juvelierizstrādājumi); Sudraba diegi; Juvelierizstrādājumi no sudraba; Juvelierizstrādājumi ar dimantiem; Zelta juvelierizstrādājumi; Rotaslietas no dzeltenā dzintara; Juvelierizstrādājumi no dārgakmeņiem; No dārgmetālu sakausējumiem izgatavoti juvelierizstrādājumi; Juvelierizstrādājumi darbinieku apbalvošanai par panākumiem; Juvelierizstrādājumu drošības ķēdītes; Juvelierizstrādājumu prezentācijas kastītes; Zeltu saturoši juvelierizstrādājumi; Gredzeni (juvelierizstrādājumi); Apsudraboti gredzeni; Zelta gredzeni; Gredzenu turētāji no cēlmetāla; Dārgakmeņu ietvari, kas ir juvelierizstrādājumu daļa; Atslēgu piekariņi [šķeltgredzeni ar greznumlietiņu vai dekoratīvu piekariņu]; Identifikācijas aproces (juvelierizstrādājumi); Ar zeltu pārklāti rokas pulksteņi; Rokassprādzes; Aproču piekariņi; Apsudrabotas rokassprādzes; Rokassprādzes (juvelierizstrādājumi); Zelta rokassprādzes; Apzeltītas rokassprādzes; Labdarības aproces; Rokassprādzes; Rokassprādzes no dārgmetāliem; Juvelierizstrādājumu ķēdītes no cēlmetāla, kas paredzētas rokassprādzēm; Pulksteņi, kas izgatavoti no cēlmetāliem vai ir ar tiem pārklāti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġojjellerija personali; Muniti mhux monetarji; Pjanċi tal-identità ta' metall prezzjuż; Arloġġi tal-platinu; Arloġġi tal-fidda; Arloġġi tal-idejn magħmula minn deheb imrembel; Arloġġi tal-idejn li jinkorporaw funzjoni tat-telekomunikazzjoni; Arloġġi tal-idejn għall-isports; Uċuħ għal arloġġi tal-idejn; Arloġġi tal-polz; Arloġġi awtomatiċi; Arloġġi mekkaniċi; Arloġġi elettriċi; Arloġġi elettriċi; Kuruni tal-arloġġi tal-id; Qafliet għal arloġġi tal-id; Arloġġi tal-idejn magħmula mid-deheb; Arloġġi tal-idejn li jinkorporaw funzjoni tal-memorja; Pawċis għal arloġġi tal-idejn; Arloġġi tal-idejn għal infermiera; Arloġġi tal-idejn li jinkludu insinja; Partijiet għall-oġġetti li jaħdmu bil-mekkaniżmu ta' arloġġ; Arloġġi tal-idejn bil-pedometri; Ġojjellerija tal-cloisonné [ġojjellerija]; Ġojjellerija tal-cloisonné [ġojjellerija]; Ġojjellerija falza; Ġada [ġojjellerija]; Ġojjellerija prezzjuża; Ġojjelli tal-enemel; Ħajt tad-deheb [ġojjellerija]; Lokits [ġojjellerija]; Ċrieket [ġojjellerija]; Brazzuletti [ġojjellerija]; Ħajt tal-fidda [ġojjellerija (Am.)]; Ġojjellerija magħmula mill-fidda; Ġojjellerija li tinkorpora d-djamanti; Ġojjellerija tad-deheb; Ġojjellerija tal-ambra safra; Ġojjellerija magħmula minn ħaġar prezzjuż; Ġojjelli magħmula minn ligi ta' metalli prezzjużi; Ġojjellerija ta' rikonoxximent korporattiv; Ktajjen bl-ilqugħ magħmul mill-ġojjelli; Kaxxi għall-preżentazzjoni tal-ġojjelli; Ġojjellerija b'kontenut ta' deheb; Ċrieket [ġojjellerija]; Ċrieket maħsulin fil-fidda; Ċrieket tad-deheb; Oġġetti għaż-żamma taċ-ċrieket, ta' metall prezzjuż; Kalettaturi li huma partijiet minn ġojjelli; Ħoloq taċ-ċwievet [ċrieki maqsuma b'ornament jew aċċessorju dekorattiv]; Brazzuletti tal-identifikazzjoni [ġojjellerija]; Arloġġi tal-idejn magħmula minn indurar tad-deheb; Brazzuletti / Ċpiepet; Oġġetti żgħar li jiddendlu mal-brazzuletti; Brazzuletti maħsula bil-fidda; Brazzuletti [ġojjellerija]; Brazzuletti tad-deheb; Brazzuletti miksija bid-deheb; Brazzuletti tal-karità; Brazzuletti / Ċpiepet; Brazzuletti ta' metall prezzjuż; Katina tal-ġojjelli ta' metall prezzjuż għal brazzuletti; Arloġġi tal-id magħmulin minn metalli prezzjużi jew miksija bihom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Persoonlijke juwelierswaren; Niet-monetaire munten; Identiteitsplaatjes van edele metalen; Platina horloges; Zilveren horloges; Horloges van bladgoud; Horloges met telecommunicatiefunctie; Sporthorloges; Wijzerplaten (voor horloges); Polshorloges; Automatische horloges; Mechanische horloges; Elektrische klokken; Elektrische klokken; Horlogekronen; Horlogegespen; Horloges van goud; Horloges met geheugenfunctie; Horlogezakjes; Horloges voor verpleegsters; Horloges met een insigne; Onderdelen voor wijzerwerken voor uurwerken; Polshorloges met pedometer; Bijouterieën in cloisonné; Bijouterieën in cloisonné; Namaakjuwelen; Jade [juwelierswaren]; Waardevolle juwelierswaren; Geëmailleerde sieraden; Gouddraad [juwelierswaren]; Medaillons [juwelierswaren]; Ringen [juwelierswaren]; Armbanden [juwelierswaren]; Gesponnen zilver; Juwelierswaren vervaardigd uit zilver; Juwelierswaren met diamanten; Juwelierswaren vervaardigd uit goud; Sieraden van barnsteen; Juwelierswaren vervaardigd uit edelstenen; Juwelierswaren vervaardigd uit legeringen van edele metalen; Sieraden als erkenning van personeel; Veiligheidskettinkjes voor sieraden; Presentatiedoosjes voor sieraden; Juwelierswaren die goud bevatten; Ringen [juwelierswaren]; Verzilverde ringen; Gouden ringen; Ringhouders van edele metalen; Ringkassen als onderdelen van juwelierswaren; Sleutelhangers; Identificatiearmbanden [juwelierswaren]; Horloges van geplateerd goud; Arm- en enkelbanden; Bedeltjes voor armbanden; Verzilverde armbanden; Armbanden [juwelierswaren]; Gouden armbanden; Armbanden (Vergulde -); Liefdadigheidsarmbanden; Arm- en enkelbanden; Armbanden van edele metalen; Sierkettingen van edele metalen voor armbanden; Horloges vervaardigd uit edele metalen of hiermee bedekt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Biżuteria osobista; Monety niesłużące do płacenia; Płytki identyfikacyjne z metali szlachetnych; Platynowe zegarki; Srebrne zegarki; Zegarki z walcowanego złota; Zegarki z funkcją komunikacji na odległość; Zegarki sportowe; Tarcze do zegarków; Zegarki; Zegarki automatyczne; Zegary mechaniczne; Zegary i zegarki elektryczne; Zegary i zegarki elektryczne; Koronki do zegarków; Klamerki do zegarków; Zegarki ze złota; Zegarki zawierające funkcję pamięci; Woreczki na zegarki; Zegarki dla pielęgniarek; Zegarki z insygniami; Części mechanizmów zegarowych; Zegarki na rękę z krokomierzem; Biżuteria z emalii komórkowej; Biżuteria z emalii komórkowej; Biżuteria ze szkła sztrasowego; Jadeit [biżuteria]; Biżuteria szlachetna; Biżuteria emaliowana; Złote nici [biżuteria]; Medaliony [biżuteria]; Pierścionki [biżuteria]; Bransoletki [biżuteria]; Nici ze srebra (biżuteria); Wyroby jubilerskie wykonane ze srebra; Biżuteria z diamentami; Biżuteria ze złota; Ozdoby z żółtego bursztynu; Biżuteria wykonana z kamieni szlachetnych; Wyroby jubilerskie wykonane ze stopów metali szlachetnych; Firmowe nagrody za osiągnięcia w postaci biżuterii; Jubilerskie łańcuszki zabezpieczające; Kasety do prezentacji wyrobów jubilerskich; Biżuteria ze złotem; Pierścionki [biżuteria]; Pierścionki powlekane srebrem; Pierścionki złote; Stojaki na pierścionki wykonane z metali szlachetnych; Oprawy będące częścią biżuterii; Breloczki do kluczy [kółka do kluczy z ozdobami lub dekoracyjnymi zawieszkami]; Bransoletki identyfikacyjne [biżuteria]; Zegarki pozłacane; Bransolety; Zawieszki do bransoletek; Bransoletki powlekane srebrem; Bransoletki [biżuteria]; Złote bransoletki; Bransoletki pozłacane; Bransoletki charytatywne; Bransolety; Bransoletki z metali szlachetnych; Łańcuszki z metali szlachetnych na bransoletki; Zegarki wykonane z metali szlachetnych lub nimi powlekane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Joalharia pessoal; Moedas não monetárias; Chapas de identificação em metais preciosos; Relógios de platina; Relógios de prata; Relógios em ouro laminado; Relógios com função de telecomunicação integrada; Relógios desportivos; Visores para relógios; Relógios de pulso; Relógios automáticos; Relógios mecânicos; Relógios elétricos; Relógios elétricos; Coroas para relógios; Fivelas para relógios; Relógios em ouro; Relógios com função de memorização incorporada; Bolsas para relógios; Relógios para enfermeiros; Relógios com insígnias; Peças para mecanismos de relógios; Relógios de pulso com conta-passos; Joias em cloisonné; Joias em cloisonné; Strass [bijuteria]; Jade [joalharia]; Joias preciosas; Artigos de joalharia esmaltados; Fios de ouro [bijutaria]; Medalhões [joalharia]; Anéis [joalharia]; Pulseiras [bijutaria]; Prata em fios; Joalharia de prata; Joalharia com diamantes incorporados; Joalharia de ouro; Jóias em âmbar amarelo; Joalharia feita de pedras preciosas; Artigos de joalharia feitos em ligas de metais preciosos; Bijuteria de identificação institucional; Correntes de joalharia; Caixas de apresentação para joalharia; Artigos de joalharia que contêm ouro; Anéis [joalharia]; Anéis revestidos de prata; Anéis de ouro; Suportes para anéis em metais preciosos; Engates para sujeitar peças de jóias; Porta-chaves [com objeto decorativo]; Pulseiras de identificação [joalharia]; Relógios revestidos em ouro; Pulseiras; Amuletos para pulseiras; Pulseiras revestidas de prata; Pulseiras [bijutaria]; Pulseiras em ouro; Pulseiras banhadas a ouro; Pulseiras associadas a projetos de beneficência; Pulseiras; Pulseiras de metais preciosos; Corrente (fio) de metais preciosos para pulseiras; Relógios de metais preciosos ou revestidos com os mesmos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bijuterii personale; Monede care nu sunt pecuniare; Plăcuţe de identificare din metal preţios; Ceasuri de mână din platină; Ceasuri de mână din argint; Ceasuri din aur laminat; Ceasuri care încorporează o funcţie de telecomunicare; Ceasuri sportive; Cadrane pentru ceasuri; Ceasuri de mână; Ceasuri automate; Ceasuri mecanice; Ceasuri electrice; Ceasuri electrice; Coroane pentru ceasuri de mână; Închizătoare pentru ceasuri; Ceasuri din aur; Ceasuri cu o funcţie de memorare; Huse pentru ceasuri de mână; Ceasuri pentru asistente; Ceasuri cu embleme; Piese de mecanism de ceas; Ceasuri de mână cu pedometre; Bijuterii cloisonne; Bijuterii cloisonne; Ştrasuri; Jad [articole de bijuterie]; Bijuterii preţioase; Bijuterii emailate; Aur filat [bijuterii]; Medalioane [bijuterii]; Inele [bijuterii]; Brăţări [bijuterii]; Fir de argint [bijuterii]; Bijuterii fabricate din argint; Bijuterii cu diamante; Bijuterii din aur; Chihlimbar (Podoabe din -); Bijuterii din pietre preţioase; Articole de bijuterie realizate din aliaje de metale preţioase; Bijuterii de recunoştinţă pentru angajaţi; Lănţişoare de siguranţă pentru bijuterii; Cutii de prezentare pentru bijuterii; Articole de bijuterie care conţin aur; Inele [bijuterii]; Inele placate cu argint; Inele din aur; Suporturi pentru inele din metale preţioase; Inele de fixare, fiind piese de bijuterie; Inele pentru chei [inele de chei cu breloc sau portchei decorativ]; Brăţări de identificare [bijuterii]; Ceasuri placate cu aur; Brăţări; Talismane pentru brăţări; Brăţări placate cu argint; Brăţări [bijuterii]; Brăţări de aur; Brăţări placate cu aur; Brăţări folosite în scop caritabil; Brăţări; Brăţări din metale preţioase; Lanţuri din metale preţioase pentru brăţări; Ceasuri de mână din metale preţioase sau placate cu acestea.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Osobné šperky; Mince pre iné ako peňažné účely; Identifikačné štítky z drahých kovov; Platinové hodinky; Strieborné hodinky; Hodinky z valcovaného zlata; Hodinky s telekomunikačnými funkciami; Športové hodinky; Ciferníky hodiniek; Hodinky; Automatické hodinky; Mechanické hodinky; Elektrické hodiny a hodinky; Elektrické hodiny a hodinky; Korunky hodiniek; Spony na hodinky; Hodinky vyrobené zo zlata; Hodinky so zabudovanou pamäťovou funkciou; Puzdra na hodiny; Hodinky pre zdravotné sestry; Hodinky s insígniou; Súčiastky hodín a hodiniek; Náramkové hodinky s krokomermi; Smaltové šperky; Smaltové šperky; Štras (brúsené olovnaté sklo); Jadeit [šperky]; Vzácne klenoty; Emailované šperky; Zlaté nite (klenotnícke výrobky); Medailóny (klenotnícke výrobky); Prstene (klenotnícke výrobky); Náramky (klenotnícke výrobky); Strieborný drôt; Šperky zo striebra; Šperky obsahujúce diamanty; Zlaté šperky; Jantárové šperky; Šperky z drahokamov; Šperkárske výrobky zo zliatin vzácnych kovov; Firemné šperky; Bezpečnostné retiazky; Krabičky na šperky; Šperky s obsahom zlata; Prstene (klenotnícke výrobky); Postriebrené prstene; Zlaté prstene; Držiaky na prstene z drahých kovov; Korunky na osadenie drahokamov ako časti šperkov; Krúžky na kľúče (s príveskom alebo ozdobou); Identifikačné náramky [šperky]; Hodinky pokované zlatom; Náramky; Prívesky na náramky; Postriebrené náramky; Náramky (klenotnícke výrobky); Zlaté náramky; Pozlátené náramky; Charitatívne náramky; Náramky; Náramky z drahých kovov; Šperkové retiazky z drahých kovov, určené pre náramky; Hodinky z drahých kovov alebo nimi pokované.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Osebni nakit; Kovanci, ki niso denar; Identifikacijske ploščice iz žlahtnih kovin; Ročne ure iz platine; Srebrne ročne ure; Ročne ure iz valjanega zlata; Ročne ure z vgrajeno telekomunikacijsko funkcijo; Športne ure; Številčnice za ročne in zapestne ure; Zapestne ure; Avtomatske ure; Mehanske ročne ure; Ure, električne; Ure, električne; Krone (gumbi za navijanje in nastavljanje ročne ure); Zaponke (sponke) za ročne ure; Ročne ure iz zlata; Ročne ure z vgrajeno pomnilniško funkcijo; Mošnjički za ročne ure; Ročne ure za medicinske sestre; Ure z insignijami; Deli za urne mehanizme; Zapestne ure s pedometri; Cloisonné nakit; Cloisonné nakit; Bižuterija (ceneni modni nakit); Žad [nakit]; Dragocen nakit; Emajliran nakit; Zlate niti [nakit]; Medaljoni [nakit]; Prstani [nakit]; Zapestnice [nakit]; Srebrna nit [nakit]; Nakit iz srebra; Nakit z diamanti; Nakit iz zlata; Nakit iz jantarja; Nakit iz dragih kamnov; Kosi nakita, izdelani iz zlitin žlahtnih kovin; Nakit za priznanje dosežkov v podjetju; Varnostna verižica za nakit; Skrinjice za razstavljanje nakita; Nakit, ki vsebuje zlato; Prstani [nakit]; Prstani, prevlečeni s srebrom; Zlati prstani; Držala za prstane iz žlahtnih kovin; Okovja, ki so del nakita; Obeski za ključe [obročki z okraskom ali dekorativnim obeskom]; Identifikacijske zapestnice [nakit]; Pozlačene ročne ure; Zapestnice; Obeski za zapestnice; Zapestnice, prevlečene s srebrom; Zapestnice [nakit]; Zlate zapestnice; Pozlačene zapestnice; Zapestnice [za dobrodelne namene]; Zapestnice; Zapestnice iz žlahtnih kovin; Verižice iz žlahtnih kovin za zapestnice; Ročne ure iz žlahtnih kovin ali prevlečene z njimi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Personliga smycken; Icke-monetära mynt; Identitetsskyltar av ädelmetall; Armbandsur av platina; Armbandsur av silver; Armbandsur av gulddoublé; Armbandsur med telekommunikationsfunktion; Armbandsur för sportanvändning; Urtavlor för armbandsur; Armbandsur; Automatiska armbandsur; Mekaniska armbandsur; Elektriska armbandsur; Elektroniska armbandsur; Kronor för armbandsur; Spännen för armbandsur; Armbandsur av guld; Armbandsur med minnesfunktion; Påsar för armbandsur; Armbandsur för sjuksköterskor; Armbandsur med insignier; Delar för armbandsur; Armbandsur med stegräknare; Cloissonné-smycken; Cloissonné (smycken); Konstgjorda smycken; Jade [smycken]; Äkta smycken; Emaljerade smycken; Guldtråd [smycken]; Medaljonger [smycken]; Ringar [smycken]; Armband [smycken]; Silvertråd [smycken]; Smycken av silver; Smycken innehållande diamanter; Smycken av guld; Smycken av bärnsten; Smycken av ädelstenar; Smycken av ädelmetallegeringar; Smycken för företagserkännande; Säkerhetskedjor för smycken; Presentationsaskar för smycken; Smycken innehållande guld; Ringar (juvelerarvaror); Silverpläterade ringar; Ringar av guld; Ringhållare av ädelmetall; Ringar som del av smycken; Nyckelringar [delade ringar med prydnader eller dekorativa emblem]; Id-armband [smycken]; Armbandsur av pläterat guld; Armband; Armbandsberlocker; Silverpläterade armband; Armband (juvelerarvaror); Armband av guld; Guldpläterade armband (juvelerarvaror); Armband för välgörenhet; Armringar och armband; Armband av ädelmetall; Smyckeskedjor av ädelmetall för armband; Armbandsur av ädla metaller eller överdragna därmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/012</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-01-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/105</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>935122</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
