<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-06-05T10:49:29</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018173417</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018173417</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-01-03</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-05-22</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-01-03</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>klarkraft</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Измервателни уреди за електричество; Слънчеви панели за производство на електричество; Фотоволтаични инсталации за генериране на електричество [фотоволтаични енергийни съоръжения]; Телекомуникационни мрежи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje na měření elektřiny; Solární panely na výrobu elektřiny; Fotovoltaická zařízení na výrobu elektrické energie [fotovoltaické elektrárny]; Telekomunikační sítě.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Elektricitetsmålende instrumenter; Solpaneler til elproduktion; Fotovoltaiske anlæg til produktion af elektricitet [fotovoltaiske kraftværker]; Telekommunikationsnetværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Strommessinstrumente und -apparate; Solarmodule für die Stromerzeugung; Photovoltaische Anlagen zur Erzeugung von Elektrizität [photovoltaische Kraftwerke]; Telekommunikationsnetze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Όργανα ηλεκτρικής μέτρησης· Φωτοβολταϊκά πλαίσια για παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού· Φωτοβολταϊκές εγκαταστάσεις για την παραγωγή ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος [φωτοβολταϊκές μονάδες παραγωγής ισχύος]· Δίκτυα τηλεπικοινωνιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electricity meters; Solar panels for production of electricity; Photovoltaic installations for generating electricity [photovoltaic power plants]; Telecommunications networks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Instrumentos para medir la electricidad; Paneles solares para producir electricidad; Instalaciones fotovoltaicas para la producción de electricidad [plantas de energía fotovoltaica]; Redes de telecomunicaciones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektrimõõturid; Päikesepaneelid elektrienergia tootmiseks; Fotogalvaanilised paigaldised elektrienergia tootmiseks [fotogalvaanilised elektrijaamad]; Telekommunikatsioonivõrgud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sähkönmittausvälineet; Aurinkopaneelit sähkön tuotantoon; Aurinkosähkölaitteistot sähköntuotantoon [aurinkosähkövoimalat]; Tietoliikenneverkot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Instruments de mesure de l'électricité; Panneaux solaires pour la production d'électricité; Installations photovoltaïques pour la production d'électricité [centrales photovoltaïques]; Réseaux de télécommunications.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Instrumenti za mjerenje električne struje; Solarne ploče za proizvodnju električne energije; Fotonaponski objekti za proizvodnju električne energije [fotonaponske elektrane]; Telekomunikacijske mreže.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elektromosságmérő berendezések; Napelemek villamosenergia-termeléshez; Fotoelektromos berendezések elektromosság termeléséhez [fotoelektromos erőművek]; Távközlési hálózatok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Strumenti per misurare l'elettricità; Pannelli solari per la produzione di energia elettrica; Installazioni fotovoltaiche per la produzione di elettricità [impianti fotovoltaici]; Reti di telecomunicazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektros matavimo prietaisai; Saulės baterijų plokštės (elektros gamybai); Fotovoltiniai elektros gamybos įrenginiai [fotovoltinės elektrinės]; Telekomunikacijos tinklų įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektriskās strāvas mērinstrumenti; Saules enerģijas paneļi elektroenerģijas ražošanai; Fotoelektriskās iekārtas, kas paredzētas elektroenerģijas ražošanai [fotoelektriskās spēkstacijas]; Telesakaru tīkli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Strumenti għall-kejl tal-elettriku; Pannelli solari għall-produzzjoni tal-elettriku; Installazzjonijiet fotovoltajċi għall-ġenerazzjoni tal-elettriku [impjanti tal-enerġija fotovoltajċi]; Netwerks tat-telekomunikazzjonijiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Instrumenten voor elektrische meting; Zonnepanelen voor het opwekken van elektriciteit; Fotovoltaïsche installaties voor de opwekking van elektriciteit [fotovoltaïsche centrales]; Telecommunicatienetwerken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przyrządy do pomiaru energii elektrycznej; Panele słoneczne do wytwarzania energii elektrycznej; Instalacje fotowoltaiczne do wytwarzania energii elektrycznej [elektrownie fotowoltaiczne]; Sieci telekomunikacyjne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Instrumentos de medição elétrica; Painéis solares para a produção de eletricidade; Instalações fotovoltaicas para a produção de eletricidade [centrais fotovoltaicas]; Redes de telecomunicações.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Instrumente pentru măsurarea electricității; Panouri solare pentru producerea energiei electrice; Instalații fotovoltaice pentru producerea de electricitate [centrale fotovoltaice]; Rețele de telecomunicații.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nástroje na meranie elektriny; Solárne panely na výrobu elektrickej energie; Fotovoltaické zariadenia pre výrobu elektriny [fotovoltaické elektrárne]; Telekomunikačné siete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Električni merilni instrumenti; Sončne plošče za proizvodnjo električne energije; Fotonapetostne instalacije za proizvodnjo električne energije [fotonapetostne elektrarne]; Telekomunikacijska omrežja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Mätinstrument avseende elektricitet; Solpaneler för produktion av elektricitet; Solcellsanläggningar för alstring av elektricitet [solcellskraftverk]; Telekommunikationsnätverk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Разчитане на електромери с цел изготвяне на сметки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Odečítání elektroměrů pro účely fakturace.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Aflæsning af elmålere til faktureringsformål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ablesen von Stromzählern zu Abrechnungszwecken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ανάγνωση μετρητών κατανάλωσης ηλεκτρισμού για σκοπούς τιμολόγησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electricity meter reading for billing purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Lectura de contadores eléctricos para fines de facturación.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektrimõõdikute lugemine arvete koostamiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sähkömittareiden lukeminen laskutustarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Relevé de compteurs électriques aux fins de facturation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Očitanje električnog brojila za potrebe obračuna.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Villanyórák leolvasása számlázási célokból.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Lettura di contatori elettrici a scopo di fatturazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektros skaitiklio rodmenų skaitymas sąskaitų sudarymo reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektroenerģijas skaitītāju rādījumi rēķinu apmaksas nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Qari elettriku tal-miter għal skopijiet ta' kont.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Het aflezen van elektriciteitsmeters voor afrekendoeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odczyt mierników elektrycznych do celów wystawiania rachunków.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Leitura de contadores elétricos para fins de faturação.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Citirea contoarelor electrice pentru facturare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odčítanie elektromerov na fakturačné účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Odčitavanje električnih števcev za namene obračunavanja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elmätaravläsning för faktureringsändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>38</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Телекомуникационни услуги; Радио телекомуникации; Информационни услуги свързани с телекомуникации; Услуги за телекомуникационен портал; Комуникации чрез клетъчни телефони; Интерактивни телекомуникационни услуги; Информационни услуги в областта на телекомуникациите; Услуги за достъп в областта на телекомуникациите; Услуги на мобилна телекомуникационна мрежа; Телефонни и телекомуникационни услуги; Телекомуникационни услуги чрез интернет; Осигуряване на електронни комуникационни връзки; Осигуряване на телекомуникационни средства; Мобилни комуникационни услуги; Услуги предоставяни чрез телекомуникационни системи; Услуги на телекомуникационна цифрова мрежа; Телекомуникационни услуги по фиксирана линия; Предоставяне на достъп до телекомуникационни мрежи; Пренос на данни по телекомуникационен път; Услуги за електронни и телекомуникационни излъчвания; Комуникации чрез мултинационални телекомуникационни мрежи; Телекомуникации чрез електронна поща; Комуникационни услуги чрез сателит; Фиброоптични телекомуникационни услуги; Предоставяне на услуги чрез телекомуникационните мрежи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Telekomunikační služby; Radiotelekomunikace; Informační služby v oblasti telekomunikací; Služby telekomunikačních bran; Komunikace prostřednictvím mobilních telefonů; Interaktivní telekomunikační služby; Informace o telekomunikaci; Telekomunikační přístupové služby; Služby mobilní telekomunikační sítě; Telefonní a telekomunikační služby; Telekomunikační služby založené na Internetu; Poskytování elektronických telekomunikačních připojení; Poskytování telekomunikačních zařízení; Služby mobilní komunikace; Provozování telekomunikačních systémů; Služby v oblasti digitálních telekomunikačních sítí; Služby pevné telekomunikační linky; Poskytování přístupu k telekomunikačním sítím; Přenos dat prostřednictvím telekomunikací; Služby v oblasti elektronického a telekomunikačního přenosu; Komunikace přes mezinárodní telekomunikační sítě; Telekomunikace prostřednictvím elektronické pošty; Satelitní telekomunikační služby; Služby v oblasti telekomunikací prostřednictvím optických vláken; Provozování telekomunikačních sítí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Telekommunikation; Radiotelekommunikationsvirksomhed; Informationstjenester i forbindelse med telekommunikation; Telekommunikationsportalstjenester; Mobiltelefonkommunikation; Interaktiv telekommunikationsvirksomhed; Stillen information til rådighed om telekommunikation; Tjenesteydelser vedrørende telekommunikationsadgang; Tjenester inden for mobile telekommunikationsnetværk; Telefon- og telekommunikationsvirksomhed; Internetbaseret telekommunikationsvirksomhed; Tilrådighedsstillelse af elektroniske telekommunikationsforbindelser; Tilvejebringelse af telekommunikationsfaciliteter; Mobiltelefonkommunikationsvirksomhed; Drift af telekommunikationssystemer; Telekommunikationsvirksomhed i forbindelse med digitale netværk; Telekommunikation via fastnet; Tilrådighedsstillelse af adgang til telekommunikationsnetværk; Overførsel af data via telekommunikation; Elektronisk transmission og transmission via telekommunikation; Kommunikation via multinationale telekommunikationsnetværk; Telekommunikation via elektronisk post; Telekommunikation via satellit; Fiberoptisk telekommunikationsvirksomhed; Drift af telekommunikationsnetværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Telekommunikationsdienste; Telekommunikation mittels Funk; Auskunftsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Telekommunikation; Telekommunikationsdienste mittels Portalen; Mobiltelefondienste; Interaktive Telekommunikationsdienste; Auskünfte über Telekommunikation; Zugriffsdienstleistungen in der Telekommunikation; Dienstleistungen von Mobiltelekommunikationsnetzen; Telefon- und Telekommunikationsdienste; Internetbasierte Telekommunikationsdienste; Bereitstellung von elektronischen Telekommunikationsverbindungen; Vermietung von Telekommunikationsausstattungen; Mobile Kommunikationsdienste; Telekommunikationsdienste für den Betrieb eines Telekommunikationssystems; Telekommunikationsdienstleistungen über digitale Netzwerke; Kabelgebundene Telekommunikationsdienste; Bereitstellen des Zugriffs auf Telekommunikationsnetzwerke; Datentransfer durch Telekommunikation; Elektronische und Telekommunikationsübertragungsdienste; Kommunikationsdienste via multinationaler Telekommunikationsnetzwerke; Telekommunikationsdienste mittels E-Mail; Satellitentelekommunikationsdienste; Faseroptische Telekommunikationsdienste; Telekommunikationsdienste für den Betrieb eines Telekommunikationsnetzwerkes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνίας· Ραδιοτηλεπικοινωνίες· Υπηρεσίες πληροφόρησης σχετικά με τις τηλεπικοινωνίες· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνιακής πύλης δικτύου· Επικοινωνία μέσω κινητών τηλεφώνων· Υπηρεσίες διαδραστικής τηλεπικοινωνίας· Πληροφόρηση τηλεπικοινωνιών· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνιακής πρόσβασης· Υπηρεσίες δικτύων κινητής τηλεπικοινωνίας· Τηλεφωνικές και τηλεπικοινωνιακές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνιών βασιζόμενες στο Διαδίκτυο (Internet)· Παροχή ηλεκτρονικών τηλεπικοινωνιακών συνδέσεων· Παροχή τηλεπικοινωνιακών εγκαταστάσεων· Υπηρεσίες κυψελοειδούς επικοινωνίας· Λειτουργία τηλεπικοινωνιακών συστημάτων· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνίας ψηφιακού δικτύου· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνιών μέσω σταθερής γραμμής· Παροχή πρόσβασης σε τηλεπικοινωνιακά δίκτυα· Μεταφορά δεδομένων μέσω τηλεπικοινωνιών· Υπηρεσίες ηλεκτρονικής και τηλεπικοινωνιακής μετάδοσης· Επικοινωνίες μέσω πολυεθνικών τηλεπικοινωνιακών δικτύων· Τηλεπικοινωνίες μέσω ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου· Υπηρεσίες δορυφορικής επικοινωνίας· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνιών οπτικών ινών· Λειτουργία τηλεπικοινωνιακού δικτύου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Telecommunication; Telecommunications; Telecommunication services; Radio telecommunications; Telecommunications information; Telecommunications portal services; Telecommunications gateway services; Cellular telecommunications services; Interactive telecommunications services; Telecommunication of information; Information about telecommunication; Telecommunication (Information about -); Telecommunication access services; Telecommunication network services; Telecommunication gateway services; Interactive telecommunication services; Telecommunications services; Mobile telecommunication network services; Telephone and telecommunication services; Internet based telecommunication services; Providing electronic telecommunication connections; Provision of telecommunication facilities; Mobile telecommunications services; Telecommunications access services; Operation of telecommunications systems; Digital network telecommunications services; Fixed line telecommunication services; Providing access to telecommunication networks; Transfer of data by telecommunication; Electronic and telecommunication transmission services; Communications via multinational telecommunication networks; Telecommunications by e-mail; Telecommunications services by satellite; Mobile telecommunications network services; Fibre optic telecommunications services; Optical fibre telecommunications services; Transfer of data by telecommunications; Information services relating to telecommunications; Operation of a telecommunications network.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de telecomunicaciones; Telecomunicaciones por radio; Servicios de información relacionados con las telecomunicaciones; Servicios de pasarela de telecomunicaciones; Servicios de comunicación por telefonía móvil; Servicios de telecomunicaciones interactivas; Información sobre telecomunicaciones; Servicios de acceso a telecomunicaciones; Servicios de redes de telecomunicaciones móviles; Servicios de telecomunicaciones y de comunicaciones telefónicas; Servicios de telecomunicación basados en Internet; Facilitación de conexiones electrónicas para telecomunicaciones; Facilitación de instalaciones de telecomunicaciones; Servicios de comunicación móvil; Funcionamiento de sistemas de telecomunicación; Servicios de telecomunicaciones de redes digitales; Servicios de telecomunicaciones de línea fija; Facilitación del acceso a redes de telecomunicación; Transferencia de datos a través de telecomunicaciones; Servicios de transmisión electrónica y de telecomunicaciones; Comunicaciones a través de redes multinacionales de telecomunicaciones; Telecomunicaciones por correo electrónico; Servicios de telecomunicaciones vía satélite; Servicios de telecomunicaciones de fibra óptica; Funcionamiento de redes de telecomunicaciones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sideteenused; Raadiotelekommunikatsioon; Telekommunikatsiooniga seotud teabeteenused; Telekommunikatsiooniportaalide teenused; Side mobiiltelefonide vahendusel; Interaktiivsed sideteenused; Sideinfo; Telekommunikatsioonile ligipääsu võimaldamine; Mobiilse telesidevõrgu teenused; Telefonside- ja telekommunikatsiooniteenused; Internetipõhised telekommunikatsiooniteenused; Elektrooniliste telekommunikatsiooniühenduste pakkumine; Siderajatiste pakkumine; Mobiilsideteenused; Telekommunikatsioonisüsteemide rakendamine; Digitaalvõrkude sideteenused; Fiksliinide kaudu edastatavad telekommunikatsiooniteenused; Telekommunikatsioonivõrkudele juurdepääsu võimaldamine; Andmete edastamine telekommunikatsiooni vahendusel; Elektrooniliste ja telekommunikatsiooniseadmete vahendusel edastamise teenused; Side rahvusvaheliste sidevõrkude kaudu; Elektronpostiside; Satelliitsideteenused; Kiudoptilise side teenused; Sidevõrkude rakendamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kaukoviestintä; Radioviestintäpalvelut; Telekommunikaatioon liittyvät tiedotuspalvelut; Televiestintäporttipalvelut; Matkapuhelinviestintä; Vuorovaikutteiset tietoliikennepalvelut; Kaukoviestintään liittyvä neuvonta; Tietoliikenneyhteyksiin liittyvät palvelut; Matkapuhelinviestintään liittyvät verkkopalvelut; Puhelin- ja tietoliikennepalvelut; Internet-pohjaiset tietoliikennepalvelut; Elektronisten tietoliikenneyhteyksien tarjoaminen; Tietoliikennemahdollisuuksien tarjoaminen; Mobiiliviestintäpalvelut; Tietoliikennejärjestelmien operointi; Digitaaliset tietoverkkopalvelut; Kiinteälinjaiset tietoliikennepalvelut; Tietoliikenneverkkojen käyttömahdollisuuden tarjoaminen; Tiedonsiirto tietoliikenteen avulla; Elektroniset ja tietoliikennelähetyspalvelut; Viestintä monikansallisten tietoliikenneverkkojen välityksellä; Tietoliikenne sähköpostin välityksellä; Satelliittiviestintäpalvelut; Valokuitutietoliikennepalvelut; Tietoliikenneverkon operaattoripalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de télécommunications; Services de radiotélécommunication; Services d'informations en matière de télécommunications; Services de passerelles de télécommunications; Services de communication par téléphones portables; Services de télécommunications interactives; Informations en matière de télécommunications; Services d'accès aux télécommunications; Services de réseaux de télécommunications mobiles; Services de téléphonie et de télécommunications; Services de télécommunications basés sur Internet; Mise à disposition de connexions de télécommunications électroniques; Mise à disposition d'infrastructures de télécommunication; Services de communication mobile; Transmission par systèmes de télécommunications; Services de télécommunications de réseaux numériques; Services de télécommunications fixes; Mise à disposition d'accès à des réseaux de télécommunications; Transfert de données par télécommunication; Services de transmission électronique de données et de télécommunication; Communications via des réseaux multinationaux de télécommunications; Télécommunications par courrier électronique; Services de communication par satellite; Services de télécommunications par fibres optiques; Transmission par réseaux de télécommunications.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Telekomunikacijske usluge; Radijske telekomunikacije; Informativne usluge u svezi s telekomunikacijama; Usluge telekomunikacijskog portala; Komunikacija mobitelima; Interaktivne telekomunikacijske usluge; Obavijesti o telekomunikacijama; Usluge telekomunikacijskog pristupa; Usluge mobilne telekomunikacijske mreže; Telefonske i telekomunikacijske usluge; Telekomunikacijske usluge putem Interneta; Omogućavanje elektroničkih telekomunikacijskih veza; Pružanje telekomunikacijskih sredstava; Usluge mobilne komunikacije; Iskorištavanje telekomunikacijskih sustava; Usluge digitalne mrežne telekomunikacije; Telekomunikacijske usluge fiksne telefonije; Omogućavanje pristupa telekomunikacijskim mrežama; Prijenos podataka putem telekomunikacije; Usluge elektroničkog i telekomunikacijskog prijenosa; Komunikacija putem multinacionalnih telekomunikacijskih mreža; Telekomunikacije putem elektroničke pošte; Komunikacijske usluge putem satelita; Usluge optičke telekomunikacije; Upravljanje telekomunikacijskom mrežom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Távközlési szolgáltatások; Rádiótávközlés; Telekommunikációval kapcsolatos információs szolgáltatások; Telekommunikációs gateway szolgáltatások; Mobiltelefonos kommunikáció; Interaktív távközlési szolgáltatások; Információszolgáltatás távközlési ügyekben; Távközlési hozzáférési szolgáltatások; Mobil telekommunikációs hálózati szolgáltatások; Telefonos és távközlési szolgáltatások; Internetalapú telekommunikációs szolgáltatások; Elektronikus távközlési összeköttetések biztosítása; Távközlési eszközök, berendezések biztosítása; Mobil kommunikációs szolgáltatások; Távközlési rendszerek működtetése; Digitális hálózati távközlési szolgáltatások; Vezetékes távközlési szolgáltatások; Távközlési hálózatokhoz való hozzáférés biztosítása; Távközlési adatátvitel; Elektronikus és távközlési továbbítási szolgáltatások; Kommunikáció multinacionális távközlési hálózatokon keresztül; E-mailes telekommunikáció; Műholdas kommunikációs szolgáltatások; Száloptikás távközlési szolgáltatások; Telekommunikációs hálózatok működtetése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di telecomunicazione; Radiotelecomunicazioni; Servizi di informazione in materia di telecomunicazioni; Servizi di portali di telecomunicazione; Servizi di comunicazione via telefoni cellurari; Servizi di telecomunicazione interattiva; Informazioni in materia di telecomunicazioni; Servizi di accesso alle reti di telecomunicazioni; Servizi di reti di telecomunicazione cellulare; Servizi di telefonia e telecomunicazioni; Servizi di telecomunicazioni mediante Internet; Fornitura di connessioni elettroniche per telecomunicazioni; Fornitura di strutture per le telecomunicazioni; Comunicazione cellulare; Gestione di sistemi di telecomunicazione; Servizi di telecomunicazione digitale; Telecomunicazioni a linea fissa; Fornitura di accesso a reti di telecomunicazione; Trasferimento di dati mediante telecomunicazioni; Servizi di trasmissione elettronica e telecomunicazione; Comunicazioni tramite reti di telecomunicazione multinazionali; Telecomunicazioni mediante posta elettronica; Servizi di telecomunicazione satellitare; Servizi di telecomunicazione a fibre ottiche; Gestione di una rete di telecomunicazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Radijo telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Informacijos paslaugos, susijusios su telekomunikacijomis; Telekomunikacijų tinklų sietuvų paslaugos; Mobiliųjų telefonų ryšiai; Sąveikiosios telekomunikacijos paslaugos; Informacija apie telekomunikacijas; Telekomunikacijų prieigos paslaugos; Judriųjų telekomunikacijų tinklų paslaugos; Telefono ir telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Internetinės telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Elektroninių telekomunikacinių ryšių teikimas; Telekomunikacijų įrangos parūpinimas; Mobiliųjų ryšių paslaugos; Telekomunikacijų sistemos; Skaitmeninio tinklo telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Fiksuoto ryšio telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Prieigos prie telekomunikacijų tinklų teikimas; Duomenų perdavimas telekomunikacijomis; Elektroninio ir telekomunikacijų perdavimo paslaugos; Ryšiai tarptautiniais telekomunikacijų tinklais; Telekomunikacijos elektroniniu paštu; Palydovinio ryšio paslaugos; Optinio pluošto telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Telekomunikacijos tinklų eksploatacija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Telesakaru pakalpojumi; Radio telekomunikācija; Informācijas pakalpojumi saistībā ar telekomunikācijām; Pakalpojumi saistībā ar telesakaru vārtejām; Mobilo tālruņu sakaru pakalpojumi; Interaktīvie telekomunikāciju pakalpojumi; Informācijas sniegšana par telesakariem; Telekomunikācijas piekļuves pakalpojumi; Mobilo telesakaru tīklu pakalpojumi; Telefona un telekomunikāciju pakalpojumi; Interneta telekomunikāciju pakalpojumi; Elektronisko sakaru savienojumu nodrošināšana; Nodrošināšana ar telekomunikāciju līdzekļiem; Mobilo sakaru pakalpojumi; Telesakaru sistēmu ekspluatācija; Telesakaru nodrošināšana ar datortīklu starpniecību; Fiksētās līnijas telekomunikācijas pakalpojumi; Piekļuves nodrošināšana telesakaru tīkliem; Datu pārsūtīšana ar telekomunikāciju starpniecību; Elektroniskas un telekomunikāciju transmisijas pakalpojumi; Sakari, izmantojot starptautiskos telekomunikāciju tīklus; Telesakari pa e-pastu; Satelītsakaru pakalpojumi; Optiskās šķiedras telekomunikāciju pakalpojumi; Telekomunikācijas tīklu ekspluatācija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi tat-telekommunikazzjoni; Telekomunikazzjonijiet bir-radju; Informazzjoni dwar servizzi tat-telekomunikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' portal tat-telekomunikazzjonijiet; Komunikazzjoni permezz ta' telefowns ċellulari; Servizzi tat-telekomunikazzjonijiet interattivi; Informazzjoni dwar telekomunikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' aċċess għat-telekomunikazzjonijiet; Servizzi tat-telekomunikazzjoni ċellulari fuq in-network; Servizzi tat-telefon u tat-telekomunikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' telekomunikazzjoni bbażati fuq l-Internet; Provvista ta' konnessjonijiet ta' telekomunikazzjoni elettronika; Provvista ta' faċilitajiet tat-telekomunikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' komunikazzjonijiet ċellulari; Tħaddim ta' sistemi tat-telekomunikazzjonijiet; Servizzi ta' telekomunikazzjonijiet b'netwerk diġitali; Servizzi tat-telekomunikazzjoni b'linja fissa; Provvista ta' aċċess għal netwerks tal-komunikazzjoni; It-trasferiment ta' data bit-telekomunikazzjoni; Servizzi tat-trasmissjoni elettronika u tat-telekomunikazzjoni; Komunikazzjoni permezz ta' netwerks ta' telekomunikazzjoni multinazzjonali; Telekomunikazzjonijiet permezz tal-posta elettronika; Servizzi ta' telekomunikazzjoni permezz ta' satellita; Servizzi ta' telekomunikazzjonijiet bil-fibra ottika; L-operat ta' network tat-telekomunikazzjonijiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Telecommunicatiediensten; Telecommunicatie via radio; Informatiediensten met betrekking tot telecommunicatie; Toegang verschaffen in het kader van telecommunicatie; Mobilofoondiensten; Interactieve telecommunicatie; Informatie op het gebied van telecommunicatie; Verlenen van toegang op het gebied van telecommunicatie; Mobiele telecommunicatienetwerkdiensten; Telefoon- en telecommunicatiediensten; Telecommunicatie via het Internet; Verschaffen van elektronische telecommunicatieverbindingen; Verstrekken van telecommunicatie-faciliteiten; Mobiele communicatiediensten; Bedienen van telecommunicatiesystemen; Digitale netwerktelecommunicatiediensten; Telecommunicatiediensten via een vaste telefoonlijn; Verschaffen van toegang tot telecommunicatienetwerken; Gegevensoverdracht door middel van telecommunicatie; Elektronische verzending en telecommunicatieverzending; Communicatie via multinationale telecommunicatienetwerken; Telecommunicatie via e-mail; Telecommunicatie via de satelliet; Telecommunicatie via glasvezels; Diensten van een telecommunicatienetwerk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi telekomunikacyjne; Telekomunikacja radiowa; Usługi informacyjne dotyczące telekomunikacji; Usługi dotyczące bramek telekomunikacyjnych; Komunikacja za pośrednictwem telefonów komórkowych; Interaktywne usługi telekomunikacyjne; Informacja o telekomunikacji; Usługi dostępu do telekomunikacji; Usługi w zakresie komórkowych sieci telekomunikacyjnych; Usługi telefoniczne i telekomunikacyjne; Usługi telekomunikacyjne świadczone w oparciu o Internet; Zapewnianie elektronicznych połączeń telekomunikacyjnych; Udostępnianie instalacji telekomunikacyjnych; Usługi w zakresie łączności ruchomej; Użytkowanie systemów telekomunikacyjnych; Usługi telekomunikacyjnej sieci cyfrowej; Usługi telekomunikacji za pośrednictwem stałego łącza; Zapewnianie dostępu do sieci telekomunikacyjnych; Przekazywanie danych za pomocą telekomunikacji; Usługi transmisji elektronicznej i telekomunikacyjnej; Komunikacja przez międzynarodowe sieci telekomunikacyjne; Telekomunikacja za pośrednictwem poczty elektronicznej; Usługi łączności satelitarnej; Usługi światłowodowej telekomunikacji; Użytkowanie sieci telekomunikacyjnej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de telecomunicações; Telecomunicações de rádio; Serviços de informação relacionados com telecomunicações; Serviços de encaminhamento de telecomunicações; Comunicações por telefones móveis; Serviços de telecomunicações interativas; Informações sobre telecomunicações; Serviços de acesso a telecomunicações; Serviços de rede de telecomunicação móvel; Serviços telefónicos e de telecomunicações; Serviços de telecomunicações baseadas na Internet; Fornecimento de ligações eletrónicas de telecomunicações; Fornecimento de instalações de telecomunicações; Serviços de comunicações móveis; Operação de sistemas de telecomunicações; Serviços de telecomunicações em redes digitais; Serviços de telecomunicações por linha fixa; Fornecimento de acesso a redes de telecomunicação; Transferência de dados através de telecomunicações; Serviços de transmissão eletrónica e de telecomunicação; Comunicações via redes de telecomunicações multinacionais; Telecomunicações através de correio eletrónico; Serviços de comunicação por satélite; Serviços de telecomunicações por fibra ótica; Operação de uma rede de telecomunicações.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de telecomunicații; Telecomunicații prin radio; Servicii de informare privind telecomunicațiile; Servicii de portaluri de telecomunicații; Comunicații prin telefoane mobile; Servicii de telecomunicații interactive; Informații în domeniul telecomunicațiilor; Servicii de accesare a telecomunicațiilor; Servicii de rețele de telecomunicații mobile; Servicii telefonice și de telecomunicații; Servicii de telecomunicații bazate pe Internet; Furnizarea de conexiuni de telecomunicații electronice; Furnizare de instalații de telecomunicații; Servicii de comunicare mobilă; Exploatare de sisteme de telecomunicații; Servicii de telecomunicații de rețele digitale; Servicii de telecomunicație prin linie fixă; Asigurarea accesului la rețele de telecomunicații; Transfer de date prin telecomunicații; Servicii de transmisie electronică și de telecomunicații; Comunicare prin rețele de telecomunicații multinaționale; Telecomunicații prin e-mail; Servicii de comunicații prin satelit; Servicii de telecomunicații prin fibră optică; Administrarea unei rețele de telecomunicații.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Telekomunikačné služby; Rádiotelekomunikačné služby; Informačné služby týkajúce sa telekomunikácií; Služby telekomunikačných brán; Komunikácia mobilnými telefónmi; Služby v oblasti interaktívnej telekomunikácie; Informácie v oblasti telekomunikácií; Prístupové služby v oblasti telekomunikácie; Služby mobilnej telekomunikačnej siete; Telefonické a telekomunikačné služby; Telekomunikačné služby založené na internete; Poskytovanie elektronického telekomunikačného pripojenia; Poskytovanie telekomunikačných zariadení; Mobilné komunikačné služby; Obsluha telekomunikačných systémov; Telekomunikačné služby v rámci digitálnej siete; Služby v oblasti pevných telekomunikačných liniek; Poskytovanie prístupu k telekomunikačným sieťam; Prenos údajov prostredníctvom telekomunikácií; Elektronické a telekomunikačné prenosové služby; Komunikácia prostredníctvom nadnárodných telekomunikačných sietí; Telekomunikácia prostredníctvom elektronickej pošty; Satelitné komunikačné služby; Telekomunikačné služby prostredníctvom optických káblov; Prevádzkovanie telekomunikačných sietí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Telekomunikacijske storitve; Radijske telekomunikacije; Informacijske storitve v zvezi s telekomunikacijami; Storitve telekomunikacijskih portalov; Komuniciranje prek mobilnih telefonov; Interaktivne telekomunikacijske storitve; Informacije o telekomunikacijah; Storitve telekomunikacijskega dostopa; Storitve mobilnega telekomunikacijskega omrežja; Telefonske in telekomunikacijske storitve; Telekomunikacijske storitve na osnovi interneta; Zagotavljanje elektronskih telekomunikacijskih povezav; Nudenje telekomunikacijskih zmogljivosti; Mobilne komunikacijske storitve; Upravljanje telekomunikacijskih sistemov; Telekomunikacijske storitve digitalnega omrežja; Storitve fiksne telekomunikacije; Zagotavljanje dostopa do telekomunikacijskih omrežij; Prenos podatkov po telekomunikacijah; Storitve elektronskega in telekomunikacijskega prenosa; Komunikacije preko mednarodnih telekomunikacijskih omrežij; Telekomunikacije preko elektronske pošte; Komunikacijske storitve preko satelita; Storitve telekomunikacij z optičnimi vlakni; Upravljanje telekomunikacijskega omrežja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Telekommunikationstjänster; Radiotelefoni; Informationstjänster med avseende på telekommunikation; Tjänster avseende telekommunikationsnätportar; Kommunikation via mobiltelefoner; Interaktiva telekommunikationstjänster; Information avseende telekommunikation; Tjänster för åtkomst av telekommunikation; Mobila telekommunikationsnättjänster; Telefon- och telekommunikationstjänster; Internetbaserade telekommunikationstjänster; Upplåtande av elektroniska telekommunikationsanslutningar; Upplåtande av telekommunikationstjänster; Mobila kommunikationstjänster; Tjänster avseende telekommunikationssystem; Telekommunikationstjänster via digitala nät; Tjänster avseende telekommunikation via fasta linjer; Upplåtande av åtkomst till telekommunikationsnätverk; Överföring av data via telekommunikationer; Elektronisk överföring och telekommunikationsöverföring; Kommunikation via multinationella telekommunikationsnät; Telekommunikationer via e-post; Telekommunikationstjänster via satellit; Fiberoptiska telekommunikationstjänster; Drift av ett telekommunikationsnät.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>39</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Акумулиране на електричество; Електроснабдяване; Електроснабдяване; Доставка и разпределение на електроенергия; Разпространяване на електричество чрез кабели; Разпределяне на електроенергия към домакинства; Разпределение и предаване на електричество; Обществени услуги от рода на разпределение на електричество; Предоставяне на информация във връзка с разпределяне на електроенергия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Skladování elektřiny; Rozvod elektřiny; Dodávka elektrické energie; Dodávka a distribuce elektrické energie; Distribuce elektrického proudu kabely; Rozvody elektrické energie do domácností; Distribuce a přenos elektřiny; Komunální služby pro rozvod elektřiny; Poskytování informací vztahujících se k rozvodu elektřiny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Lagring af elektricitet; Elektricitetsdistribution; Elektricitetsforsyning; Elektricitetsforsyning og -distribution; Distribution af elektricitet via kabler; Forsyning af elektricitet til husholdninger; Distribution og udsendelse af elektricitet; Offentligt forsyningsværk i form af distribution af elektricitet; Formidling af information vedrørende distribution af elektricitet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Elektrizitätsspeicherung [Lagerung]; Verteilung von Elektrizität; Verteilung von Elektrizität zur Stromversorgung; Stromversorgung durch Verteilung von Elektrizität; Verteilung von Elektrizität über Leitungen; Verteilung von Energie an Haushalte; Verteilung und Weiterleitung von Elektrizität; Öffentliche Versorgungsdienste in Form von Elektrizitätsverteilung; Zurverfügungstellen von Informationen im Bereich der Energieverteilung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αποθήκευση ηλεκτρισμού· Ηλεκτροδότηση· Ηλεκτροδότηση· Παροχή και διανομή ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος· Διανομή ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος μέσω συρμάτων· Διανομή ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος σε νοικοκυριά· Διανομή και μεταφορά ηλεκτρισμού· Υπηρεσίες κοινής ωφέλειας με τη μορφή διανομής ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος· Παροχή πληροφοριών σε σχέση με τη διανομή ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electricity storage; Electricity distribution; Storage of electricity; Electricity supply services; Distribution of electricity; Electricity distribution services; Supply of electricity; Electricity distribution and supply; Electricity supply and distribution; Electricity distribution via cables; Electricity distribution via wires; Distribution of electricity to households; Distribution and transmission of electricity; Public utility services in the nature of electricity distribution; Providing information relating to the distribution of electricity.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Almacenamiento de electricidad; Distribución de electricidad; Suministro de electricidad; Distribución y suministro de electricidad; Distribución de electricidad vía cables; Distribución de electricidad a hogares; Distribución y transmisión de electricidad; Suministro de energía eléctrica como servicio de utilidad pública; Suministro de información sobre la distribución de electricidad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektrienergia hoiustamine; Elektrienergia jaotamine; Elektrienergia jaotamine; Elektrienergiaga varustamine ja selle jaotamine; Elektrienergia jaotus läbi kaablite; Majapidamiste varustamine elektrienergiaga; Elektrienergia jaotus ja ülekanne; Kommunaalteenused elektrienergia jaotuse alal; Elektrijaotussüsteemide teave.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sähkön varastointi; Sähkönjakelu; Sähkönsiirto; Sähkönsyöttö ja -jakelu; Sähkönjakelu kaapelien välityksellä; Sähkön jakelu kotitalouksiin; Sähkön jakelu ja siirto; Sähkönjakeluun liittyvät julkispalvelut; Sähkön jakeluun liittyvän tiedon tarjoaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Stockage d'électricité; Distribution d'électricité; Approvisionnement en électricité; Alimentation et distribution d'électricité; Distribution d'électricité par câbles; Distribution d'électricité dans les foyers; Distribution et transmission d'électricité; Services publics de distribution d'électricité; Mise à disposition d'informations en matière de distribution d'électricité.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Skladištenje električne energije; Opskrba električnom energijom; Opskrba električnom energijom; Opskrba električnom energijom i njena distribucija; Distribucija električne energije putem kablova; Distribucija električne energije kućanstvima; Distribucija i prijenos električne energije; Komunalne usluge u obliku distribucije električne energije; Pružanje informacija o distribuciji električne energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elektromosság tárolása; Áramellátás; Áramellátás; Villamosenergia szolgáltatás és ellátás; Kábeles áramelosztás; Áramellátás háztartások számára; Elektromos energia átvitele és elosztása; Közműszolgáltatások villamosenergia-elosztás formájában; Áramellátással kapcsolatos tájékoztatás.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Accumulazione di elettricità; Distribuzione dell'elettricità; Erogazione di elettricità; Erogazione e distribuzione di energia elettrica; Distribuzione di elettricità mediante cavi; Distribuzione di elettricità domestica; Distribuzione e trasmissione di elettricità; Servizi pubblici, ovvero erogazione di energia elettrica; Fornitura di informazioni inerenti la distribuzione di elettricità.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektros energijos saugojimas; Elektros energijos paskirstymas; Elektros tiekimas; Elektros tiekimas ir skirstymas; Elektros energijos paskirstymas kabeliais; Elektros energijos skirstymas namų ūkiams; Elektros energijos paskirstymas ir perdavimas; Komunalinės paslaugos, būtent elektros energijos paskirstymas; Informacijos, susijusios su elektros paskirstymu, teikimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektrības uzglabāšana; Elektrības sadale; Elektrības piegāde; Elektroenerģijas piegāde un sadale; Elektroenerģijas sadale, izmantojot kabeļus; Elektroenerģijas sadale mājsaimniecībām; Elektrības sadale un piegāde; Elektrības sadales komunālie pakalpojumi; Informācijas sniegšana par elektrības sadali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħażna ta' elettriku; Provvista ta' elettriku; Provvista ta' elettriku; Provvista u distribuzzjoni ta' elettriku; Distribuzzjoni tal-elettriku permezz tal-kejbils; Distribuzzjoni ta' elettriku fid-djar; Distribuzzjoni u trasmissjoni ta' elettriku; Servizzi ta' utilitajiet pubbliċi f'għamla ta' distribuzzjoni tal-elettriku; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar id-distribuzzjoni tal-elettriku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Opslag van elektriciteit; Elektriciteitsvoorziening; Elektriciteitsvoorziening; Elektriciteitslevering en -voorziening; Elektriciteitsdistributie via draden; Distributie van elektriciteit aan huishoudens; Distributie en toevoer van elektriciteit; Openbare nutsdiensten in de vorm van elektriciteitsvoorziening; Informatieverstrekking met betrekking tot de distributie van elektriciteit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Magazynowanie energii elektrycznej; Dostawa energii elektrycznej; Dostawa energii elektrycznej; Dostawa i dystrybucja energii elektrycznej; Dystrybucja energii elektrycznej za pośrednictwem kabli; Dystrybucja energii elektrycznej do gospodarstw domowych; Dystrybucja i przesyłanie prądu elektrycznego; Usługi komunalne w postaci dystrybucji energii elektrycznej; Udostępnianie informacji związanych z dystrybucją elektryczności.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Armazenamento de eletricidade; Distribuição de eletricidade; Fornecimento de eletricidade; Abastecimento e distribuição de eletricidade; Distribuição de eletricidade através de fios; Distribuição de eletricidade ao domicílio; Distribuição e transmissão de eletricidade; Serviços de utilidade pública na área da distribuição de eletricidade; Disponibilização de informação sobre distribuição de eletricidade.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Stocarea energiei electrice; Distribuție de energie electrică; Furnizare energiei electrice; Furnizare și distribuție de energie electrică; Distribuție de electricitate prin intermediul cablurilor; Distribuire de electricitate în locuințe; Distribuția și transmiterea energiei electrice; Servicii publice de distribuție a energiei electrică; Furnizare de informații cu privire la distribuția electricității.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Skladovanie elektriny; Rozvod elektriny; Rozvod elektriny; Dodávka a distribúcia elektrickej energie; Rozvod elektriny pomocou káblov; Rozvod elektriny do domácností; Distribúcia a prenos elektriny; Komunálne služby týkajúce sa dodávok elektriny; Poskytovanie informácií o distribúcii elektriny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Skladiščenje električne energije; Distribucija elektrike; Oskrba z električno energijo; Oskrba in distribucija električne energije; Distribucija elektrike prek kablov; Distribucija električne energije do gospodinjstev; Distribucija in prenos elektrike; Komunalne storitve v obliki distribucije električne energije; Nudenje informacij v zvezi z distribucijo električne energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lagring av elektricitet; Eldistribution; Leverans av elektricitet; Tillhandahållande och distribution av elektricitet; Eldistribution via ledningar; Distribution av elektricitet till hushåll; Distribution och överföring av elektricitet; Eldistribution (samhällsservice); Tillhandahållande av information avseende distribution av elektricitet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>40</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Произвеждане на електричество; Прозвеждане на газ и електричество; Генериране на електричество от геотермална енергия; Генериране на електричество от енергия от вятъра; Генериране на електричество от енергия от морските вълни; Генериране на електричество чрез соларна енергия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Výroba (generování) elektřiny; Výroba plynu a elektřiny; Výroba elektřiny z geotermální energie; Generování elektřiny z větrné energie; Generování elektřiny z energie z vln; Výroba elektřiny ze sluneční energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Elproduktion; Produktion af gas og elektricitet; Elproduktion på basis af geotermisk energi; Elproduktion på basis af vindenergi; Elproduktion på basis af bølgeenergi; Elproduktion på basis af solenergi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Stromerzeugung; Gas- und Stromerzeugung; Erzeugung von Elektrizität aus Erdwärme; Stromerzeugung aus Windenergie; Stromerzeugung aus Wellenenergie; Stromerzeugung aus Solarenergie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού· Παραγωγή αερίου και ηλεκτρισμού· Παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού από γεωθερμική ενέργεια· Παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού από αιολική ενέργεια· Παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού από κυματική ενέργεια· Παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού από την ηλιακή ενέργεια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electricity generating; Electricity generation; Generation of electricity; Generating of electricity; Generation of gas and electricity; Generation of electricity from geothermal energy; Generation of electricity from wind energy; Generation of electricity from wave energy; Generation of electricity from solar energy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Generación de electricidad; Generación de gas y electricidad; Generación de electricidad a partir de energía geotérmica; Generación de electricidad a partir de energía eólica; Producción de electricidad a partir de energía undimotriz; Generación de electricidad a partir de energía solar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektri tootmine; Elektri- ja gaasitootmine; Maapõueenergiast elektri tootmine; Tuuleenergiast elektri tootmine; Elektrienergia tootmine laineenergiast; Elektrienergia tootmine päikeseenergiast.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sähköntuotanto; Kaasun ja sähkön tuotanto; Sähkön tuottaminen maalämpöenergian avulla; Sähköntuotanto tuulivoimalla; Sähköntuotanto aaltovoimalla; Sähköntuotanto aurinkoenergiasta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Production d'électricité; Génération de gaz et d'électricité; Génération d’électricité à partir d’énergie géothermique; Production d'électricité à partir de l'énergie éolienne; Production d'électricité à partir de l'énergie des vagues; Production d'électricité à partir de l'énergie solaire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Generiranje električne energije; Proizvodnja plina i električne energije; Proizvodnja električne energije iz geotermalne energije; Proizvodnja električne energije pomoću energije vjetra; Proizvodnja električne energije pomoću energije valova; Proizvodnja električne energije iz solarne energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elektromos áram fejlesztése; Gáz- és áramfejlesztés; Áramfejlesztés geotermikus energiából; Áram szélenergiából való előállítása; Elektromos áram hullámenergiából történő előállítása; Áram előállítás napenergiából.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Generazione di elettricità; Produzione di gas e di elettricità; Generazione di elettricità da energia geotermica; Produzione di elettricità dall'energia eolica; Produzione di elettricità dall'energia del moto ondoso; Generazione di elettricità per mezzo di energia solare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektros energijos generavimas; Dujų ir elektros energijos gamyba; Elektros energijos gamyba naudojant geoterminę energiją; Elektros energijos gamyba naudojant vėjo energiją; Elektros energijos gamyba naudojant bangų energiją; Elektros energijos gamyba naudojant saulės energiją.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektrības ražošana; Gāzes un elektrības ražošana; Elektrības ražošana no ģeotermālās enerģijas; Elektrības ražošana no vēja enerģijas; Elektrības ražošana no viļņu enerģijas; Elektrības ražošana no saules enerģijas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġenerazzjoni tal-elettriku; Ġenerazzjoni ta' gass u elettriku; Ġenerazzjoni tal-elettriku mill-enerġija ġeotermali; Ġenerazzjoni ta' elettriku mill-enerġija mir-riħ; Ġenerazzjoni ta' elettriku permezz tal-enerġija mill-mewġ; Ġenerazzjoni ta' elettriku permezz tal-enerġija solari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Elektriciteitsopwekking; Opwekken van gas en elektriciteit; Het opwekken van elektriciteit uit geothemische energie; Opwekken van elektriciteit uit windenergie; Opwekken van elektriciteit uit golfenergie; Opwekking van elektriciteit uit zonne-energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wytwarzanie elektryczności; Wytwarzanie gazu i prądu elektrycznego; Wytwarzanie energii elektrycznej z energii geotermalnej; Wytwarzanie energii elektrycznej z energii wiatru; Wytwarzanie energii elektrycznej z energii fal; Wytwarzanie elektryczności z energii słonecznej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produção de eletricidade; Produção de gás e eletricidade; Produção de eletricidade a partir de energia geotérmica; Produção de energia elétrica a partir de energia eólica; Geração de eletricidade a partir de energia das ondas; Produção de eletricidade a partir de energia solar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Generare de electricitate; Generarea gazelor și electricității; Generare de electricitate din energie geotermală; Generare de electricitate din energia eoliană; Generarea de electricitate din energia valurilor; Generarea electricității din energie solară.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Výroba elektrickej energie; Výroba plynu a elektriny; Výroba elektrickej energie z geotermálnej energie; Výroba elektriny z veternej energie; Výroba elektriny z energie vĺn; Výroba elektriny zo slnečnej energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Proizvodnja elektrike; Proizvodnja plina in elektrike; Proizvodnja električne energije iz geotermalne energije; Pridobivanje elektrike iz vetrne energije; Pridobivanje elektrike iz energije valov; Proizvodnja elektrike iz sončne energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elgenerering; Alstring av gas och elektricitet; Alstring av elektricitet från geotermisk energi; Alstring av elektricitet från vindenergi; Generering av elektricitet ur vågenergi; Alstring av elektricitet från solenergi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PriorityDetails>
<Priority>
<PriorityCountryCode>NO</PriorityCountryCode>
<PriorityNumber>201913530</PriorityNumber>
<PriorityDate>2019-10-13</PriorityDate>
<PriorityPartialIndicator>false</PriorityPartialIndicator>
<PriorityStatusCode>Claimed</PriorityStatusCode>
</Priority>
</PriorityDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/011</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-01-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/105</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1057481</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
