<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-05-18T17:15:03</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018173424</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018173424</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-01-04</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="2" status="3">Application withdrawn</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>hotukdeals</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Рекламиране на стоки и услуги на други чрез интернет; Рекламиране на стоки и услуги за трети лица чрез реклами в интернет сайтове; Рекламиране на стоки и услуги за други чрез световна компютърна мрежа; Промотиране на стоки и услуги за трети лица чрез компютър и комуникационни мрежи; Поместване на реклами за трети лица; Пей пър клик реклама; Разпространение на реклами.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagace zboží a služeb pro třetí osoby prostřednictvím internetu; Propagace výrobků a služeb jiných subjektů prostřednictvím reklamy na internetových stránkách; Propagace zboží a služeb pro třetí osoby prostřednictvím globální počítačové sítě; Propagace zboží a služeb třetích osob prostřednictvím počítačových a komunikačních sítí; Umisťování reklam pro třetí osoby; PPC reklama; Šíření reklamních materiálů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Markedsføring af produkter og tjenesteydelser for andre på internettet; Promovering af andres varer og tjenesteydelser via annoncering på websider på internettet; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andres varer og tjenesteydelser via et globalt computernetværk; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andres varer og tjenesteydelser via computer- og kommunikationsnetværk; Placering af reklamer og annoncer for andre; Pay per click reklame; Spredning af reklamemateriale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbepräsentation von Waren und Dienstleistungen anderer im Internet; Verkaufsförderung für Waren und Dienstleistungen von Dritten durch Werbung auf Internet-Seiten; Verkaufsförderung für Waren und Dienstleistungen Dritter über globales Computernetz; Verkaufsförderung für Waren und Dienstleistungen Dritter über Computer- und Kommunikationsnetze; Platzierung von Anzeigen für Dritte; Pay-per-Click-Werbung; Verbreitung von Werbeanzeigen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προώθηση των αγαθών και υπηρεσιών άλλων μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Προώθηση αγαθών και υπηρεσιών που προσφέρονται από άλλους, μέσω διαφήμισης σε διαδικτυακούς ιστοχώρους· Προώθηση των αγαθών και υπηρεσιών άλλων μέσω παγκόσμιου ηλεκτρονικού δικτύου· Προώθηση των προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών τρίτων μέσω ηλεκτρονικών δικτύων και δικτύων επικοινωνίας· Καταχώριση διαφημίσεων για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Διαφήμιση με πληρωμή ανά κλικ· Διανομή διαφημιστικών μηνυμάτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Promoting the goods and services of others over the Internet; Promoting the goods and services of others through advertisements on Internet websites; Promoting the goods and services of others via a global computer network; Promoting the goods and services of others via computer and communication networks; Placing advertisements for others; Pay per click advertising; Dissemination of advertising matter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Promoción de productos y servicios de terceros por Internet; Promoción de productos y servicios de terceros mediante anuncios en sitios web; Promoción de productos y servicios de terceros por redes informáticas mundiales; Promoción de productos y servicios de terceros a través de redes informáticas y de comunicaciones; Colocación de anuncios para terceros; Servicios publicitarios de pago por clic; Difusión de anuncios publicitarios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste müügiedendus Interneti kaudu; Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste müügiedendus internetireklaami abil; Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste müügiedendus ülemaailmse arvutivõrgu kaudu; Kolmandate isikute toodete ja teenuste müügiedendus arvuti- ja sidevõrgu kaudu; Kuulutuste ülespanemisteenused teistele; Klikipõhine reklaamimine; Reklaammaterjalide levitamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden ja palveluiden myynninedistäminen Internetissä; Tavaroiden ja palvelujen myynninedistäminen kolmansien osapuolten lukuun Internet-sivustoilla tarjottavan mainonnan kautta; Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden ja palveluiden myynninedistäminen maailmanlaajuisessa tietokoneverkossa; Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden ja palveluiden myynninedistäminen tietokone- ja viestintäverkkojen välityksellä; Mainosten sijoittelu muiden lukuun; Maksu per klikkaus mainonta; Mainosten jakelu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de promotion des produits et services de tiers par Internet; Promotion de biens et services pour le compte de tiers au moyen de publicité sur des sites internet; Services de promotion des produits et services de tiers par le biais de réseaux informatiques mondiaux; Promotion des produits et services de tiers via des réseaux informatiques et de communication; Emplacement de publicités pour des tiers; Services publicitaires facturables au clic; Diffusion d'annonces publicitaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Promocija robe i usluga drugih putem Interneta; Promidžba proizvoda i usluga za treće putem oglašavanja na internetskim stranicama; Promocija robe i usluga drugih putem globalne računalne mreže; Promocija proizvoda i usluga trećih osoba putem informacijskih i komunikacijskih mreža; Postavljanje reklama za druge; Oglašavanje plaćanjem po kliku; Razdioba reklamnih oglasa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Harmadik személyek termékeinek és szolgáltatásainak Interneten való reklámozása; Harmadik fél termékeinek és szolgáltatásainak promóciója weboldalakon elhelyezett reklámokkal; Harmadik személyek áruinak és szolgáltatásainak globális számítógépes hálózaton keresztül történő reklámozása; Mások áruinak és szolgáltatásainak reklámozása számítógépes és kommunikációs hálózatokon keresztül; Szolgáltatás reklámok elhelyezésére; Pay Per Click (PPC) hirdetés; Reklámterjesztés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Promozione di prodotti e servizi per conto terzi tramite internet; Promozione di beni e servizi per conto terzi tramite pubblicità su siti internet; Promozione di prodotti e servizi per conto terzi tramite una rete informatica globale; Promozione di prodotti e servizi per conto terzi mediante reti informatiche e di comunicazione; Collocazione di annunci pubblicitari per conto terzi; Servizi pubblicitari fatturabili con un click [click advertising]; Diffusione di annunci pubblicitari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kitų tiekėjų prekių ir paslaugų reklamavimas internete; Prekių ir paslaugų reklama kitiems per skelbimus interneto svetainėse; Kitų tiekėjų prekių ir paslaugų skatinimas globaliu kompiuteriniu tinklu; Kitų prekių ir paslaugų reklamavimas kompiuterių ir ryšių tinklais; Reklamos kitiems skelbimas; Reklama "mokėk už paspaudimą"; Reklaminių skelbimų platinimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Preču un pakalpojumu veicināšana internetā citiem; Preču un pakalpojumu veicināšana trešām personām, izmantojot reklāmu interneta vietnēs; Preču un pakalpojumu veicināšanas pakalpojumi citiem, izmantojot globālo datortīklu; Trešo personu preču un pakalpojumu veicināšana, izmantojot datoru un komunikāciju tīklus; Reklāmas izvietošana citu personu interesēs; Tādu reklāmu izvietošana internetā, klikšķinot uz kurām tiek atvērtas tīmekļa vietnes ar reklamējamo saturu un samaksa par kurām ir atkarīga no klikšķinājumu skaita; Reklāmas materiālu izdalīšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Il-promozzjoni ta' oġġetti u servizzi ta' oħrajn fuq l-Internet; Promozzjoni ta' prodotti u servizzi għal oħrajn permezz ta' riklami fuq websajts; Il-promozzjoni ta' oġġetti u servizzi ta' terzi persuni permezz ta' netwerk globali tal-kompjuter; Promozzjoni tal-oġġetti u servizzi ta' oħrajn permezz ta' netwerks informatiċi u tal-komunikazzjoni; It-tpoġġija ta' reklami għal oħrajn; Reklamar li jitħallas għal kull klikk (pay per click advertising); Tixrid ta' reklami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Promoten van goederen en diensten van anderen op het internet; Promotie van goederen en diensten voor rekening van derden via reclame op internetsites; Promotie van goederen en diensten van derden via een wereldwijd computernetwerk; Promotie van goederen en diensten van derden via computer- en communicatienetwerken; Het plaatsen van advertenties voor derden; Reclamediensten betaalbaar per klik; Verspreiding van reclameboodschappen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Promowanie towarów i usług osób trzecich w Internecie; Promowanie towarów i usług osób trzecich za pośrednictwem reklam na stronach internetowych; Promowanie towarów i usług osób trzecich za pośrednictwem globalnych sieci komputerowych; Promowanie towarów i usług osób trzecich przez sieci komputerowe i komunikacyjne; Zamieszczanie ogłoszeń dla osób trzecich; Reklama typu "płać za kliknięcie"; Rozpowszechnianie reklam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Promoção de produtos e serviços de terceiros através da Internet; Promoção de produtos e serviços de terceiros através de anúncios em websites da internet; Promoção de produtos e serviços de terceiros através de uma rede informática mundial; Promoção de produtos e serviços de terceiros através de redes informáticas e de comunicações; Colocação de anúncios para terceiros; Serviços publicitários através de PPC (pay-per-click); Difusão de anúncios publicitários.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Promovarea produselor și serviciilor altor persoane prin internet; Promovare de produse și servicii ale terților prin intermediul anunțurilor publicitare pe pagini de Internet; Promovare de produse și servicii ale altor persoane prin intermediul unei rețele globale de calculatoare; Promovare de bunuri și servicii ale terților prin intermediul rețelelor de calculatoare și de comunicații; Plasarea de anunțuri publicitare pentru terți; Publicitate de tip pay-per-click (PPC); Difuzare de anunțuri publicitare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Propagovanie tovaru a služieb klientov prostredníctvom internetu; Propagácia tovarov a služieb pre tretie osoby prostredníctvom reklamy na internetových stránkach; Propagovanie tovarov a služieb pre tretie osoby prostredníctvom globálnej počítačovej siete; Propagovanie tovarov a služieb klientov prostredníctvom počítačových a komunikačných sietí; Umiestňovanie reklám pre iné firmy a osoby; Platené reklamné služby typu „klikni sem"; Rozširovanie reklamných oznamov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Promocija blaga in storitev drugih na internetu; Promocija blaga in storitev za druge z oglaševanjem na internetnih spletnih mestih; Promocija blaga in storitev drugih preko svetovnega računalniškega omrežja; Promocija izdelkov in storitev drugih po računalniških in komunikacijskih omrežjih; Nameščanje oglasov za druge; Oglaševanje po načelu plačaj na klik; Širjenje oglasov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reklam för varor och tjänster via internet åt andra; Marknadsföring av varor och tjänster åt andra via webbplatsreklam; Marknadsföring av varor och tjänster åt andra via ett globalt datornät; Marknadsföring av andras varor och tjänster via dator- och kommunikationsnät; Placering av annonser för andras räkning; Reklamtjänster via betala-per-klick; Spridning av reklamannonser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>38</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Телекомуникационни услуги; Услуги, свързани с излъчване на радио- и телевизионни предавания; Аудиовизуални комуникационни услуги; Комуникации чрез електронни средства; Обмен на данни чрез телекомуникация; Предоставяне на достъп до форуми (услуги на чат стаи) за социални мрежи; Комуникационни услуги; Услуги на електронни информационни агенции; Предаване на информация за търговски цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Telekomunikační služby; Služby rozhlasového a televizního vysílání; Služby audiovizuální komunikace; Komunikace pomocí elektronických prostředků; Předávání dat prostřednictvím telekomunikací; Služby diskusních místností pro sociální sítě; Komunikační služby; Služby elektronických informačních agentur; Přenos informací pro obchodní účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Telekommunikation; Udsendelse af radio- og fjernssynsprogrammer; Audiovisuelle telekommunikationsydelser; Kommunikation via elektroniske medier; Kommunikation af data ved hjælp af telekommunikation; Chatrumtjenester til sociale netværk; Telekommunikationsydelser; Elektroniske nyhedsbureauer; Transmission af information i forbindelse med forretningsvirksomhed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Telekommunikationsdienste; Ausstrahlung von Rundfunk- und Fernsehprogrammen; Audiovisuelle Kommunikationsdienste; Kommunikationsdienste über elektronische Medien; Übertragung von Daten mittels Telekommunikation; Bereitstellung von Internet-Chatrooms für soziale Netzwerke; Kommunikationsdienste; Elektronische Dienste von Nachrichtenagenturen; Übertragung von Informationen für Geschäftszwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνίας· Ραδιοτηλεοπτικές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες οπτικοακουστικής επικοινωνίας· Επικοινωνία με ηλεκτρονικά μέσα· Επικοινωνία δεδομένων μέσω τηλεπικοινωνιών· Υπηρεσίες χώρων συζήτησης για κοινωνική δικτύωση· Υπηρεσίες επικοινωνίας· Ηλεκτρονικές υπηρεσίες ειδησεογραφικών πρακτορείων· Μετάδοση πληροφοριών για επιχειρηματική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Telecommunications; Broadcasting services; Audiovisual communication services; Communication by electronic means; Communication of data by means of telecommunications; Chatroom services for social networking; Communications services; Electronic news agency services; Transmission of information for business purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de telecomunicaciones; Servicios de radiodifusión; Servicio de comunicación audiovisual; Comunicación a través de medios electrónicos; Comunicación de datos por medio de telecomunicaciones; Servicios de salas de chat para redes sociales; Servicios de comunicaciones; Servicios electrónicos de agencias de información; Transmisión de información destinada a los negocios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sideteenused; Ringhäälinguteenused; Audiovisuaalsideteenused; Side elektrooniliste vahendite kaudu; Andmeside telekommunikatsioonivahendite kaudu; Jututoateenused sotsiaalseks võrgusuhtluseks; Sideteenused; Elektroonilised uudisteagentuuride teenused; Teabe edastamine äriotstarbeks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kaukoviestintä; Lähetyspalvelut; Audiovisuaaliset viestintäpalvelut; Viestintä elektronisten välineiden avulla; Datan välitys tietoliikenteen avulla; Keskustelukanavapalvelut sosiaalista verkottumista varten; Viestintäpalvelut; Sähköiset uutistoimistopalvelut; Tiedonsiirto liiketoimintatarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de télécommunications; Services de diffusion; Service de communication audiovisuelle; Communication par voie électronique; Communication de données par voie de télécommunications; Services de salons de discussion [chat] en ligne pour réseaux sociaux; Services de communication [télécommunications]; Services d'agences d'information par voie électronique; Transmission d'informations à des fins commerciales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Telekomunikacijske usluge; Usluge emitiranja; Usluge audiovizualne komunikacije; Komunikacija putem elektroničkih sredstava; Prijenos podataka putem telekomunikacije; Usluge soba za čavrljanje za društvene mreže; Komunikacijske usluge; Usluge elektroničkih novinskih agencija; Prijenos informacija u poslovne svrhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Távközlési szolgáltatások; Műsorszórási szolgáltatások; Audiovizuális kommunikációs szolgáltatások; Kommunikáció elektronikus eszközökkel; Adatok közlése távközlési eszközökkel; Közösségi hálózatok csevegőszoba szolgáltatásai; Kommunikációs szolgáltatások; Elektronikus hírügynökségi szolgáltatások; Információtovábbítás üzleti célokra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di telecomunicazione; Servizi via cavo; Servizi di comunicazione audiovisiva; Comunicazione tramite mezzi elettronici; Comunicazione di dati mediante telecomunicazioni; Servizi di chat-room per collegamento in reti sociali; Servizi di comunicazione; Agenzie di informazioni elettroniche; Trasmissione d'informazioni per uso aziendale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Transliavimo paslaugos; Garso ir vaizdo ryšio paslaugos; Ryšiai elektroninėmis priemonėmis; Duomenų perdavimas telekomunikacijų priemonėmis; Pokalbių svetainių paslaugos socialinių ryšių tinklo reikmėms; Ryšių paslaugos; Elektroninių naujienų agentūros paslaugos; Informacijos perdavimas verslo reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Telesakaru pakalpojumi; Apraides pakalpojumi; Audiovizuālo sakaru pakalpojumi; Sakari, izmantojot elektroniskos līdzekļus; Datu komunikācija, izmantojot telekomunikāciju līdzekļus; Tērzētavas pakalpojumi sociālajai tīklošanai; Sakaru pakalpojumi; Elektronisko ziņu aģentūru pakalpojumi; Informācijas pārraide uzņēmējdarbības mērķiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi tat-telekommunikazzjoni; Servizzi tax-xandir; Servizzi ta' komunikazzjoni awdjoviżivi; Komunikazzjoni b'mezzi elettroniċi; Komunikazzjoni ta' dejta permezz tat-telekomunikazzjonijiet; Servizzi ta' siti tal-iċċettjar għal netwerking soċjali; Servizzi ta' komunikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-aħbarijiet b'mod elettroniku; Trasmissjoni ta' informazzjoni għal skopijiet ta' negozju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Telecommunicatiediensten; Uitzenddiensten; Audiovisuele communicatiediensten; Communicatie via elektronische middelen; Overdracht van gegevens door middel van telecommunicatie; Chatroomdiensten voor sociale netwerken; Communicatiediensten; Electronische nieuwsdiensten; Overdracht van informatie voor zakelijke doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi telekomunikacyjne; Usługi transmisyjne; Usługi łączności audiowizualnej; Komunikacja za pomocą środków elektronicznych; Przesyłanie danych za pośrednictwem telekomunikacji; Usługi pokojów rozmów [chatroom] dla serwisów społecznościowych; Usługi łączności; Usługi elektronicznej agencji prasowej; Transmisja informacji do celów biznesowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de telecomunicações; Serviços de radiodifusão; Serviços de comunicação audiovisual; Comunicação por meios eletrónicos; Comunicação de dados através de telecomunicações; Serviços de sala de conversação para atividades de rede social; Serviços de comunicação; Serviços de agências de notícias eletrónicas; Transmissão de informações para fins comerciais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de telecomunicații; Servicii de transmisie; Servicii de comunicații audiovizuale; Comunicare prin mijloace electronice; Comunicare de date prin mijloace de telecomunicații; Servicii de chatroom pentru rețele sociale; Servicii de comunicații; Servicii de agenții de știri electronice; Transmitere de informații în scopuri de afaceri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Telekomunikačné služby; Vysielacie služby; Audiovizuálne komunikačné služby; Komunikácia pomocou elektronických prostriedkov; Komunikácia údajov prostredníctvom telekomunikácií; Služby diskusných miestností pre sociálne siete; Komunikačné služby; Služby elektronických spravodajských agentúr; Prenos informácií na obchodné účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Telekomunikacijske storitve; Storitve radijskega in televizijskega oddajanja; Avdiovizualne komunikacijske storitve; Komunikacija po elektronskih sredstvih; Komunikacija podatkov s telekomunikacijskimi sredstvi; Storitve klepetalnic za družabno mreženje; Komunikacijske storitve; Storitve elektronskih tiskovnih agencij; Prenos informacij za poslovne namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Telekommunikationstjänster; Mediasändningstjänster; Audiovisuella kommunikationstjänster; Kommunikation via elektroniska medel; Kommunikation av data med hjälp av telekommunikation; Chattjänster för sociala nätverk; Kommunikationstjänster; Elektroniska nyhetsbyråer; Sändning av information för företagsändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<SeniorityDetails>
<Seniority>
<SeniorityCountryCode>GB</SeniorityCountryCode>
<SeniorityApplicationNumber>2592128</SeniorityApplicationNumber>
<SeniorityFilingDate>2011-08-17</SeniorityFilingDate>
<SeniorityRegistrationNumber>2592128</SeniorityRegistrationNumber>
<SeniorityRegistrationDate>2012-09-28</SeniorityRegistrationDate>
<InternationalTradeMarkCode>EU</InternationalTradeMarkCode>
<SeniorityPartialIndicator>false</SeniorityPartialIndicator>
<SeniorityStatusCode>Accepted</SeniorityStatusCode>
</Seniority>
</SeniorityDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1057498</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>68207</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
