<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-26T07:46:13</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018173432</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018173432</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-01-05</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-01-05</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-26</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CARLEEF&amp;IRENE</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекло; Долни дълги гащи [облекло]; Връхни палта; Трикотажно и плетено облекло; Анорак; Горни дрехи с висока яка; Трика за акробати; Тениски; Поли; Рокли; Сака; Къси наметки; Панталони за йога; Комплекти за новородени [дрехи]; Шалове; Шалчета; Шапки и принадлежности за глава; Къси чорапи; Ръкавици; Спортни обувки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy; Spodky; Svrchníky; Pletené oděvní výrobky; Parky; Roláky; Trikotové kombinézy [úplé oblečení s nohavicemi]; Trička; Sukně; Dámské šaty; Kabáty; Peleríny; Kalhoty na jógu; Výbavy pro novorozence [oděvy]; Šály; Šátky a šály; Pokrývky hlavy; Ponožky; Rukavice [oděvy]; Sportovní vyšší obuv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande; Bukser; Overfrakker; Strikkede beklædningsgenstande; Parkacoats; Rullekravebluser; Trikoter med ben og fødder; T-shirts; Nederdele; Kjoler; Frakker; Slængkapper; Yogabukser; Babytøj; Sjaler; Tørklæder; Hattemagervarer; Sokker; Handsker [beklædning]; Sportsstøvler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke; Unterhosen; Überzieher [Bekleidung]; Strickwaren [Bekleidung]; Parkas; Rollkrägen; Gymnastikanzüge; T-Shirts; Röcke; Damenkleider; Mäntel; Capes; Yogahosen; Babywäsche; Stolen; Schals; Hüte; Socken; Handschuhe [Bekleidung]; Sportschuhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα· Σώβρακα· Πανωφόρια· Πλεκτά [ενδύματα]· Άνορακ· Ζιβάγκο· Ολόσωμες εφαρμοστές φόρμες χορού· Μπλουζάκια (τι-σερτ)· Φούστες· Βραδινές τουαλέτες· Μπουφάν· Κάπες· Παντελόνια για γιόγκα· Μωρουδιακά· Σάλια (ενδύματα)· Μαντήλια για το λαιμό· Είδη πιλοποιίας· Κάλτσες· Γάντια· Αθλητικά υποδήματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothes; Pants; Top coats; Knitwear; Parkas; Turtlenecks; Bodysuits; T-shirts; Skirts; Dresses; Coats; Capes; Yoga pants; Baby layettes for clothing; Shawls; Scarves; Hats; Socks; Gloves; Athletics shoes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Prendas de vestir; Calzones; Gabanes; Prendas de punto; Parkas; Prendas superiores de cuello alto; Mallas; Camisetas [de manga corta]; Faldas; Vestidos; Abrigos; Capas; Pantalones de yoga; Ajuares de bebé [prendas de vestir]; Chales; Fulares; Sombreros; Calcetines; Guantes [prendas de vestir]; Calzado de deporte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad; Aluspüksid; Ülekuued, mantlid, palitud; Kudumid (rõivad); Parkad; Rullkaelusega kampsunid, sviitrid; Pikad võimlemistrikood; T-särgid; Seelikud; Kleidid; Kasukad, mantlid; Peleriinid; Joogapüksid; Imikupesu; Sallid, rätikud; Sallid; Kübarad, vormimütsid; Sokid; Kindad (rõivad); Spordisaapad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet; Miesten alushousut; Päällystakit; Neulevaatteet; Anorakit ja hupputakit; Poolopaidat; Sukkapuvut; T-paidat; Hameet; Kaavut; Takit; Lyhyet viitat; Joogahousut; Vauvanvaatteet; Hartiahuivit ja saalit; Huivit; Päähineet; Sukat; Käsineet; Lenkkitossut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements; Caleçons; Pardessus; Tricots [vêtements]; Parkas; Cols roulés; Justaucorps longs; Tee-shirts; Jupes; Robes; Manteaux; Capes et pèlerines; Pantalons de yoga; Layettes; Châles; Foulards; Chapeaux; Chaussettes; Gants [habillement]; Chaussures de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjeća; Muške gaće; Muški ogrtači; Pletena odjeća [odjevni predmeti]; Parke [sportske jakne s kapuljačom]; Dolčevite; Triko-unitard; Majice kratkih rukava; Suknje; Dugačke haljine; Jakne; Pelerine; Hlače za jogu; Oprema za bebe; Šalovi; Rupci [fulari]; Pokrivala za glavu; Muške čarape; Rukavice; Sportska obuća.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházati cikkek; Nadrágok; Szövetkabátok, felöltők; Kötöttáruk [ruházat]; Parkák; Garbó nyakú felsők; Tánc unitard [balett-trikók, táncruhák]; Pólók; Szoknyák; Talárok; Kabátok, dzsekik; Pelerin, köpeny; Jóganadrágok; Csecsemőkelengyék, babakelengyék; Vállkendők, nagykendők; Sálak; Kalapáruk; Zoknik; Kesztyűk; Sportcipők.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Abbigliamento; Mutande; Soprabiti; Indumenti lavorati a maglia; Parka; Dolcevita; Tutine sportive; Tee-shirt; Gonne; Abiti; Cappotti; Cappe; Pantaloni da yoga; Corredini da neonato; Scialli; Foulards [fazzoletti]; Cappelli; Calzini; Guanti [abbigliamento]; Calzature per lo sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, apranga; Moteriškos kelnaitės; Apsiaustai; Megzti drabužiai; Striukės su gobtuvu; Megztiniai aukšta apykakle (golfai); Ištisiniai triko; Marškinėliai; Sijonai; Suknelės; Paltai; Pelerinos; Jogos kelnės; Kraiteliai [kūdikių drabužiai]; Skaros; Šalikai; Galvos apdangalai; Puskojinės; Pirštinės [drabužiai]; Sportinė avalynė.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi; Vīriešu bikses; Garie mēteļi; Adījumi (apģērbi); Parkas; Apģērbi ar augsto apkakli; Bodiji vingrošanai; T-krekli; Svārki; Kleitas; Mēteļi; Pelerīnes; Jogas bikses; Zīdaiņu pūriņi (apģērbs); Plecu lakati; Šalles; Cepures; Īsās zeķes; Cimdi; Zābaki sportam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies; Qliezet; Kappotti; Xogħol tal-malja [lbies]; Parkas; Flokkijiet turtlenecks; Ilbiesi sħaħ issikkati għaż-żfin [unitards]; Flokkijiet forma ta' T [T-shirts]; Dbielet; Ilbiesi twal tan-nisa; Ġkieket; Kapep; Qliezet tal-joga; Il-ġhieżi tat-trabi (ilbies); Xalel; Xalpi; Xedd ir-ras; Kalzetti; Ingwanti; Żraben tal-isports.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleding; Broeken (Lange -); Overjassen; Gebreide kleding; Parka's; Coltruien; Gympakjes; T-shirts; Rokken; Japonnen; Mantels; Capes; Yogabroeken; Baby-uitzet [kleding]; Sjaals; Halsdoeken; Hoofddeksels; Sokken; Handschoenen [kleding]; Sportschoeisel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież; Slipy męskie, figi damskie; Palta; Dzianina [odzież]; Kurtki z kapturem chroniące przed zimnem i wiatrem; Golfy; Trykoty z długimi nogawkami; Koszulki z krótkim rękawem; Spódnice; Długie luźne stroje; Kurtki; Peleryny [narzutki]; Spodnie do jogi; Wyprawki dziecięce [odzież]; Szale; Szaliki; Nakrycia głowy; Skarpetki; Rękawiczki; Buty sportowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário; Ceroulas; Sobretudos [vestuário]; Malhas [vestuário]; Parkas; Camisolas de gola alta; Malhas para ginástica; T-shirts; Saias; Vestidos; Casacos; Capas; Calças de ioga; Enxovais [vestuário]; Xailes; Cachecóis; Chapéus; Meias; Luvas [vestuário]; Botas para desporto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Izmene; Paltoane; Tricoturi [îmbrăcăminte]; Haine tip parka; Bluze cu guler pe gât; Costume de gimnastică; Tricouri; Fuste; Rochii lungi de seară; Jachete; Cape și pelerine; Pantaloni pentru yoga; Trusouri [articole de îmbrăcăminte]; Șaluri; Eșarfe; Articole pentru acoperirea capului; Șosete; Mănuși [articole de îmbrăcăminte]; Încălțăminte de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy; Nohavice; Zvrchníky; Pleteniny (oblečenie); Parky (teplé krátke kabáty s kapucňou); Roláky; Trikoty s dlhými nohavicami; Tričká; Sukne; Šaty; Kabáty; Peleríny; Nohavice na cvičenie jogy; Oblečenie pre bábätká; Pletené šatky; Šatky, šály; Pokrývky hlavy; Ponožky; Rukavice; Športová obuv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila; Spodnjice; Površniki; Pletenine [oblačila]; Parke (daljše jakne s kapuco); Puliji; Enodelno oblačilo iz raztegljivega materiala, ki pokriva celo telo; Majice s kratkimi rokavi; Ženska krila; Halje; Plašči; Pelerina; Hlače za jogo; Oblačila za novorojenčke; Šali; Ovratne rute; Pokrivala; Kratke nogavice; Rokavice; Športni čevlji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder; Byxor; Överrockar; Trikåvaror [kläder]; Parkasar; Halvpolotröjor; Hela gymnastikdräkter [unitards]; T-shirtar; Kjolar; Klänningar; Rockar; Caper; Yogabyxor; Babyutstyrslar [kläder]; Sjalar; Scarves; Hattar; Sockor; Handskar; Boots för sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Телевизионни реклами; Пей пър клик реклама; Рекламни агенции; Отдаване под наем на рекламно място във влакове; Рекламиране чрез пощенски поръчки; Онлайн реклама в компютърна мрежа; Подготвяне на рекламни материали; Продуктови демонстрации и продуктово представяне; Рекламни услуги по пощатата; Рекламни текстове (Публикуване на -); Консултация по бизнес управление; Администрация на бизнес дела за франчайзинг; Предоставяне на бизнес информация чрез уебсайт; Посреднически бизнес услуги относно свързването на потенциални частни инвеститори с предприемачи, нуждаещи се от финансиране; Агенции за внос и износ; Услуги, свързани с провеждане на пазарни изследвания; Телемаркетингови услуги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagace; Televizní reklama; PPC reklama; Zprostředkování propagace; Pronájem reklamní plochy ve vlacích; Zásilková reklama; Online inzerce v počítačové síti; Příprava reklamních materiálů; Služby předvádění výrobků a vystavování zboží; Cílené zasílání reklamních materiálů; Vydávání reklamních textů; Poradenství v oblasti řízení obchodní činnosti; Správa obchodních věcí v oblasti franšíz; Poskytování obchodních informací prostřednictvím webových stránek; Zprostředkování obchodů v oblasti propojení možných soukromých investorů s podnikateli, kteří potřebují financování; Zprostředkování dovozu a vývozu; Provádění marketingových studií; Telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Reklamevirksomhed; TV-reklamer; Pay per click reklame; Reklamebureauvirksomhed; Leasing af reklameplads på tog; Annoncering pr. postordre; Online-annoncering på et computernetværk; Udarbejdelse af reklamemateriale; Fremvisning og demonstration af produkter; Avertering pr. post; Publikation af reklametekster; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse; Administration af forretningsanliggender i forbindelse med franchisevirksomhed; Stillen forretningsinformation til rådighed via et websted; Forretningsmægling i forbindelse med matchning af potentielle private investorer med iværksættere, der mangler kapital; Import- og eksportagenturer; Gennemførelse af marketingundersøgelser; Telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung; Fernsehwerbung; Pay-per-Click-Werbung; Dienstleistungen einer Werbeagentur; Vermietung von Werbeflächen in Zügen; Versandwerbung; Online-Werbung in einem Computernetzwerk; Aufbereiten von Werbematerial; Produktvorführungen und -präsentationen; Verteilung von Werbematerial [Flugblätter, Prospekte, Drucksachen, Warenproben]; Herausgabe von Werbetexten; Beratung in Fragen der Geschäftsführung; Verwaltung der geschäftlichen Angelegenheiten von Franchise-Unternehmen; Bereitstellung von Geschäftsinformationen über eine Website; Kommerzielle Vermittlungsdienste, die potentielle private Investoren mit kapitalsuchenden Unternehmern zusammenbringen; Dienstleistungen einer Im- und Exportagentur; Leitung von Marketingstudien; Telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση· Διαφημιστικά τηλεοπτικά μηνύματα· Διαφήμιση με πληρωμή ανά κλικ· Πρακτορεία διαφημιστικά· Χρηματοδοτική εκμίσθωση διαφημιστικού χώρου σε τρένα· Διαφήμιση με αλληλογραφία· Διαφήμιση on line σε δίκτυο πληροφορικής· Προετοιμασία διαφημιστικού υλικού· Υπηρεσίες επιδείξεις και προβολής προϊόντων· Υπηρεσίες διαφημιστικού ταχυδρομείου· Δημοσίευση διαφημιστικών κειμένων· Παροχή επιχειρηματικών συμβουλών· Διοίκηση των επιχειρηματικών υποθέσεων αλυσίδων δικαιόχρησης· Παροχή επιχειρηματικών πληροφοριών μέσω δικτυακού τόπου· Υπηρεσίες επιχειρηματικής διαμεσολάβησης σε σχέση με αντιστοίχιση υποψήφιων ιδιωτικών επενδυτών με επιχειρηματίες που χρειάζονται χρηματοδότηση· Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Διεξαγωγή μελετών μάρκετινγκ· Υπηρεσίες τηλεμπορίας (τηλεμάρκετινγκ).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising; Advertising and publicity services; Television advertising; Pay per click advertising; Services of advertising agencies; Leasing of advertising space on trains; Advertising by mail order; On-line advertising on computer networks; On-line advertising on computer communication networks; Drafting of publicity material; Product demonstrations and product display services; Direct mail advertising services; Publication of advertising texts; Business management consulting services; Administration of the business affairs of franchises; Providing business information via a web site; Business intermediary services relating to the matching of potential private investors with entrepreneurs needing funding; Import and export agencies; Conducting marketing studies; Telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad; Publicidad televisada; Servicios publicitarios de pago por clic; Servicios de agencias de publicidad; Alquiler de espacios publicitarios en trenes; Publicidad por correspondencia; Publicidad en línea por una red informática; Preparación de material publicitario; Servicios de demostración y prueba de productos; Distribución de material publicitario [folletos, prospectos, impresos, muestras]; Publicación de textos publicitarios; Consultoría sobre dirección de negocios; Administración de asuntos de negocios de franquicias; Suministro de información comercial por sitios web; Servicios de intermediarios comerciales en el marco de la puesta en relación de potenciales inversores privados con empresarios que necesitan financiación; Servicios de agencias de importación-exportación; Realización de estudios de marketing; Servicios de telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam; Telereklaam; Klikipõhine reklaamimine; Reklaamiagentuuriteenused; Rongidel reklaamipinna üürimine; Postimüügireklaam; Arvutivõrgureklaam; Reklaammaterjalide ettevalmistamine; Toodete demonstreerimise ja väljapaneku teenused; Posti teel reklaami levitamine; Reklaamtekstide publitseerimine, avaldamine; Äritegevuse juhtimise konsultatsioonid; Frantsiisidega seotud äritegevuse juhtimine; Äriinfo pakkumine veebilehekülgedel; Ärivahendusteenused potentsiaalsete erainvestorite ja rahastamist vajavate ettevõtjate kokkuviimiseks; Ekspordi- ja impordiagentuuride teenused; Turu-uuringute teostamine; Telemarketingiteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta; Televisiomainokset; Maksu per klikkaus mainonta; Mainostoimistot; Junissa olevan mainostilan liisaus; Postimyyntimainonta; Online-mainonta tietoverkoissa; Mainosmateriaalin valmisteleminen; Tuote-esittelyt ja tuotteiden näytteillepanopalvelut; Suorapostimainonta; Mainoslehtisten julkaisu; Liikkeenhoidon konsultointi; Franchising-liiketoiminnan hallinnointi; Liiketoimintatietojen tarjoaminen verkkosivuston välityksellä; Liiketoiminnalliset välittäjäpalvelut, jotka liittyvät potentiaalisten yksityisten sijoittajien ja rahoitusta tarvitsevien yrittäjien yhteen saattamiseen; Tuonti- ja vientiagentuuripalvelut; Markkinointitutkimukset; Puhelinmyyntipalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité; Publicité télévisée; Services publicitaires facturables au clic; Services d'agences de publicité; Location d'espaces publicitaires dans des trains; Publicité par correspondance; Publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique; Préparation de matériel publicitaire (rédaction); Services de présentation et de démonstration de produits; Distribution de matériel publicitaire [tracts, prospectus, imprimés, échantillons]; Publication de textes publicitaires; Consultation pour la direction des affaires; Services administratifs relatifs aux affaires commerciales de franchises; Informations commerciales par le biais de sites web; Services d'intermédiaires commerciaux dans le cadre de la mise en relation d'éventuels investisseurs privés avec des entrepreneurs à la recherche de financements; Services d'agences d'import-export; Réalisation d'études de marketing; Services de télémarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje; Televizijsko reklamiranje; Oglašavanje plaćanjem po kliku; Agencije za promidžbu; Zakup oglasnog prostora na vlakovima; Reklamiranje putem pošte; Online oglašavanje na računalnim mrežama; Priprema reklamnog materijala; Usluge predstavljanja i izlaganja proizvoda; Raspačavanje reklamnog materijala [traktata, prospekata, tiskanica, uzoraka]; Objavljivanje promidžbenih tekstova; Konzultacije u svezi vođenje poslova; Upravljanje poslovnim aktivnostima franšiza; Pružanje poslovnih informacija putem web-stranice; Usluge poslovnog posredovanja u pogledu povezivanja potencijalnih privatnih ulagača s poduzetnicima kojima je potrebno financiranje; Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Vođenje marketinških studija; Usluge telemarketinga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; Televíziós reklámozás; Pay Per Click (PPC) hirdetés; Reklámügynökségek, hirdetési ügynökségek; Reklámhely bérbeadása vonatokon; Reklámlevél szolgáltatás; On-line hirdetői tevékenység számítógépes hálózaton; Reklámanyag készítése; Termékbemutatók és termék megjelenítési szolgáltatások; Reklámanyagok [röplapok, prospektusok, nyomtatványok, áruminták] terjesztése; Reklámszövegek publikálása; Üzletvezetési konzultáció; Franchise-zal kapcsolatos üzleti ügyek adminisztrációja; Üzleti információk nyújtása weboldalon keresztül; Üzleti közvetítési szolgáltatások potenciális magánbefektetők és tőkét igénylő vállalkozók összehozásával kapcsolatosan; Import-export ügynökségek; Marketing tanulmányok készítése; Telemarketing szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità; Pubblicità televisiva; Servizi pubblicitari fatturabili con un click [click advertising]; Servizi di agenzie di pubblicità; Affitto di spazi pubblicitari su treni; Pubblicità per corrispondenza; Pubblicità online su rete informatica; Preparazione di materiale pubblicitario; Servizi di dimostrazione e di esposizione di prodotti; Distribuzione di materiale pubblicitario [volantini, prospetti, stampati, campioni]; Pubblicazione di testi pubblicitari; Consulenza per la gestione degli affari; Amministrazione degli affari commerciali di affiliati; Informazioni commerciali diffuse tramite siti web; Servizi di intermediazione commerciale in relazione alla messa in contatto di potenziali investitori privati con imprese che necessitano di finanziamenti; Servizi di agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Studi di marketing; Servizi di telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama; Televizijos reklama; Reklama "mokėk už paspaudimą"; Reklamos agentūrų paslaugos; Reklamos vietų traukiniuose nuoma; Reklamos pristatymas paštu; Viešasis elektroninis reklamavimas kompiuterių tinkle; Reklaminės medžiagos rengimas; Prekių rodymas ir pateikimas; Reklama paštu; Reklaminių tekstų skelbimas; Verslo vadybos konsultacijos; Verslo reikalų, susijusių su franšize, administravimas; Verslo informacijos teikimas visuotinio kompiuterių tinklo svetainėse; Verslo tarpininkavimo paslaugos parenkant verslininkams privačius investuotojus; Importo ir eksporto agentūrų paslaugos; Rinkodaros nagrinėjimas; Telerinkodaros paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāma; Televīzijas reklāmu veidošana; Tādu reklāmu izvietošana internetā, klikšķinot uz kurām tiek atvērtas tīmekļa vietnes ar reklamējamo saturu un samaksa par kurām ir atkarīga no klikšķinājumu skaita; Reklāmas aģentūru pakalpojumi; Reklāmas laukumu iznomāšana vilcienos; Reklāma ar pasta starpniecību; Reklāma tiešsaistē ar datortīklu starpniecību; Reklāmas materiālu sagatavošana; Preču demonstrēšanas un izstādīšanas pakalpojumi; Reklāmas pakalpojumu nodrošināšana ar pasta starpniecību; Reklāmas tekstu publicēšana; Konsultāciju sniegšana uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Uzņēmējdarbības franšīzu administrēšana; Uzņēmējdarbības informācijas nodrošināšana tīmekļa vietnēs; Starpniecības pakalpojumi uzņēmējdarbībā starp potenciālajiem privātajiem investoriem un uzņēmējiem, kam nepieciešams finansējums; Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Mārketinga pētījumu veikšana; Telemārketinga pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar; Produzzjoni ta' reklami televiżivi; Reklamar li jitħallas għal kull klikk (pay per click advertising); Aġenziji tar-reklamar; Kiri ta' spazju tar-reklamar fuq ferroviji; Reklamar permezz ta' ordni bil-posta; Reklamar onlajn fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters; Il-preparazzjoni ta' materjal għar-reklamar; Servizzi ta' dimostrazzjonijiet tal-prodotti u displej tal-prodotti; Reklamar dirett bil-posta; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' testi pubbliċitarji; Konsulenza fil-ġestjoni ta' negozju; Amministrazzjoni tal-affarijiet tan-negozju ta' frankiġji; Forniment ta' informazzjoni dwar negozju permezz ta' sit web; Servizzi ta' intermedjarji tan-negozju relatati mat-tqabbil ta' investituri privati potenzjali ma' intraprendituri li għandhom bżonn fondi; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni u esportazzjoni; It-tmexxija ta' studji dwar il-kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Servizzi ta' telepromozzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Publiciteit; Reclame per televisie; Reclamediensten betaalbaar per klik; Diensten van reclamebureaus; Verhuur van reclameruimte op treinen; Publiciteit per post; Reclame [on-line] op een computernetwerk; Samenstellen van reclamemateriaal; Demonstreren en tentoonstellen van producten; Verspreiding van reclamemateriaal [vlugschriften, prospectussen, drukwerken, monsters]; Uitgave van reclameteksten; Advisering inzake bedrijfsvoering; Administratieve diensten inzake de commerciële zaken van franchiseondernemingen; Handelsinformatie via websites; Zakelijke bemiddeling met betrekking tot het matchen van potentiële private investeerders met ondernemers die financiering behoeven; Diensten van import- en exportagentschappen; Marketingstudies; Telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama; Reklamy telewizyjne; Reklama typu "płać za kliknięcie"; Agencje reklamowe; Wynajem powierzchni reklamowej w pociągach; Reklama korespondencyjna; Reklama online za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowej; Przygotowywanie materiałów reklamowych; Usługi w zakresie wystaw i prezentacji produktów; Bezpośrednia reklama pocztowa; Publikowanie tekstów reklamowych; Doradztwo w zakresie zarządzania biznesem; Administrowanie działalnością gospodarczą w zakresie franchisingu; Udostępnianie informacji o działalności gospodarczej za pośrednictwem strony internetowej; Usługi pośrednictwa biznesowego dotyczące kontaktowania ze sobą potencjalnych inwestorów prywatnych z przedsiębiorcami potrzebującymi finansowania; Usługi agencji importowo-eksportowych; Prowadzenie badań marketingowych; Telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade; Publicidade pela televisão; Serviços publicitários através de PPC (pay-per-click); Serviços de agências de publicidade; Aluguer de espaço publicitário em comboios; Publicidade por correspondência; Publicidade online numa rede informática; Preparação de material publicitário; Demonstração de produtos e serviços de exibição de produtos; Distribuição de material publicitário [folhetos, prospetos, impressos, amostras]; Publicação de textos publicitários; Consultadoria para direção de negócios comerciais; Administração de assuntos de negócios de franquias; Fornecimento de informações comerciais através de um website; Serviços de intermediação comercial relacionados com a aproximação de potenciais investidores privados com empresários com necessidade de financiamento; Serviços de agências de importação-exportação; Execução de estudos de marketing; Serviços de telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate; Publicitate televizată; Publicitate de tip pay-per-click (PPC); Agenții de publicitate; Închiriere de spații publicitare în trenuri; Publicitate prin corespondență; Publicitate on-line într-o rețea informatizată; Realizare de material publicitar; Prezentări de produse și servicii de afișare a produselor; Publicitate directă prin poștă; Publicare de texte publicitare; Consultanță pentru conducerea afacerilor; Administrarea afacerilor în sistem de franciză; Furnizare de informații de afaceri prin intermediul unui site; Servicii de intermediere de afaceri cu privire la corelarea potențialilor investitori privați cu antreprenorii care au nevoie de finanțare; Agenții de import-export; Efectuarea studiilor de marketing; Servicii de telemarketing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklama; Televízna reklama; Platené reklamné služby typu „klikni sem"; Reklamné agentúry; Prenájom reklamných priestorov na vlakoch; Zásielkové reklamné služby; Online reklama na počítačovej komunikačnej sieti; Zostavovanie reklamných materiálov; Predvádzanie a vystavovanie tovaru; Rozširovanie reklamných materiálov zákazníkom (letáky, prospekty, tlačoviny, vzorky); Vydávanie reklamných textov; Poradenstvo pri riadení podnikov; Správa obchodných záležitostí franchisingových podnikov; Poskytovanie obchodných informácií prostredníctvom webových stránok; Obchodné sprostredkovateľské služby v oblasti priraďovania potenciálnych súkromných investorov k podnikateľom, ktorí žiadajú o financovanie; Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Vedenie marketingových štúdií; Telemarketingové služby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Reklamno oglaševanje po televiziji; Oglaševanje po načelu plačaj na klik; Oglaševalske agencije; Zakup oglasnega prostora na vlakih; Reklamiranje po pošti; Spletno oglaševanje preko računalniškega omrežja; Priprava oglasnega gradiva; Storitve promocije in razstavljanja izdelkov; Neposredno oglaševanje po pošti; Objavljanje reklamnih besedil; Poslovodno svetovanje; Administracija poslovnih zadev franšiz; Nudenje poslovnih informacij preko spletne strani; Poslovne posredniške storitve v zvezi s povezovanjem potencialnih zasebnih vlagateljev s podjetniki, ki potrebujejo finančna sredstva; Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Izvajanje tržnih študij; Storitve telemarketinga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reklam; Tv-reklamverksamhet; Reklamtjänster via betala-per-klick; Reklambyråer; Uthyrning av annonseringsutrymme på tåg; Annonsering via postorder; Annonsering online via datanätverk; Utarbetande av annons- och reklammaterial; Demonstration och visning av produkter; Direktreklam; Publicering av reklamtexter; Konsulttjänster avseende management; Administration av affärsverksamhet för franchiseföretag; Tillhandahållande av affärsinformation via en webbsida; Affärsmellanhänder på området matchning av potentiella privatinvesterare och entreprenörer i behov av finansiering; Import-exportagenturer; Utförande av marknadsföringsstudier; Telemarketingtjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/005</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-01-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/162</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-26</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1057523</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>69891</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018150899</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>69891</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-10</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
