<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-03T12:27:49</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018173419</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018173419</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-01-04</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-30</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-01-04</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-03</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ENSPOWAY</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Хронографи [времезаписващи апарати]; Електронни везни; Измервателни линии; Електрически фенери [светлинни сигнали]; Домофони; Апарати за глобално позициониране; Слушалки; Безжични тонколони; Телескопи; Спасителни шамандури; Преносими аварийни интеркоми; Персонални аларми за сигурност; Електрически звънци за врати; Предупредителни устройства против кражби; Рамки за пенснета; Очила [оптични]; Калъфи за очила; Зарядни устройства за мобилни телефони; Батерии, електрически.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Chronografy [přístroje na zaznamenávání času]; Elektronické váhy; Pravítka se stupnicí; Blikače [světelná signalizace]; Interkomy, zařízení pro vnitřní spojení; Přístroje pro určování polohy; Sluchátka; Bezdrátové reproduktory; Teleskopy; Záchranné kruhy; Přenosné nouzové interkomy; Osobní bezpečnostní poplašná zařízení; Elektrické dveřní zvonky; Výstražná zařízení proti krádeži; Brýlové obroučky; Brýle; Pouzdra na brýle; Nabíječky baterií do mobilních telefonů; Elektrické baterie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kronografer [tidsmålingsapparater]; Elektroniske vægte; Linealer til måling; Blinksignaler; Apparater til intercom; Anordninger til global positionering; Høretelefoner; Trådløse højttalere; Teleskoper; Redningskranse; Bærbare samtaleanlæg til anvendelse i nødsituationer; Personlige sikkerhedsalarmer; Elektriske ringeapparater til døre; Tyverialarmer; Brillestel; Briller [optik]; Etuier til briller; Batteriopladere til mobiltelefoner; Batterier, elektriske.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Chronografen [Zeiterfassungsgeräte]; Elektronische Waagen; Messstäbe; Blinker [Lichtsignale]; Wechselsprechgeräte; Globale Ortungsgeräte; Kopfhörer; Kabellose Lautsprecher; Fernrohre; Rettungsbojen; Tragbare Notruf-Gegensprechanlagen; Persönliche Sicherheitsmelder; Türklingeln [elektrisch]; Diebstahlalarmgeräte; Brillenfassungen, -gestelle; Brillen [Optik]; Brillenetuis; Akkuladegeräte für Mobiltelefone; Elektrische Batterien.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χρονογράφοι [συσκευές καταγραφής χρόνου]· Ηλεκτρονικοί ζυγοί· Χάρακες μέτρησης· Λαμπτήρες αποστολής φωτεινών σημάτων· Θυροτηλέφωνα· Συσκευές παγκόσμιου προσδιορισμού θέσης· Ακουστικά· Ασύρματα ηχεία· Τηλεσκόπια· Ζώνες σωστικές· Φορητές συσκευές ενδοεπικοινωνίας εκτάκτου ανάγκης· Προσωπικοί συναγερμοί ασφαλείας· Κουδουνάκια για πόρτες ηλεκτρικά· Συναγερμοί αντικλεπτικοί· Σκελετοί γυαλιών· Διόπτρες· Επιρρίνιων γυαλιών οράσεως θήκες· Φορτιστές μπαταριών για κυψελοειδή τηλέφωνα· Ηλεκτρικές μπαταρίες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Chronographs [time recording apparatus]; Electronic scales; Measuring rules; Blinkers [signalling lights]; Intercoms; GPS navigation device; Earphones; Wireless speakers; Telescopes; Life buoys; Portable emergency intercoms; Personal security alarms; Electric door bells; Burglar alarms; Frames for spectacles; Eye glasses; Spectacle cases; Cell phone battery chargers; Batteries,electric.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cronógrafos [aparatos para registrar el tiempo]; Balanzas electrónicas; Reglas graduadas; Luces de destello [señales luminosas]; Interfonos; Dispositivos de posicionamiento global; Auriculares; Altavoces inalámbricos; Telescopios; Salvavidas; Intercomunicadores de emergencia portátiles; Alarmas de seguridad personal; Timbres de puerta eléctricos; Alarmas antirrobo; Monturas de gafas; Gafas [óptica]; Estuches para gafas; Cargadores de baterías de teléfonos móviles; Pilas eléctricas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kronograafid [ajaregistreerimisaparaadid]; Elektroonilised kaalud; Joonlauad (mõõtmiseks); Vilkurid [signaaltuled]; Sisesuhtlusvahendid; GPS-seadmed; Kõrvaklapid; Juhtmeta kõlarid; Teleskoobid; Päästepoid; Kaasaskantavad hädaabi-sisetelefonid; Turvaalarmid eraisikutele; Elektrilised uksekellad; Vargusvastane signalisatsioon; Prilliraamid; Prillid [optika]; Prillitoosid; Mobiiltelefonide akulaadurid; Elektripatareid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kronografit [ajanrekisteröintilaitteet]; Elektroniset vaa'at; Mittapuut; Suuntavilkut; Sisäpuhelimet; Maailmanlaajuiset paikannuslaitteet; Kuulokkeet; Langattomat kaiuttimet; Kaukoputket; Pelastusliivit; Kannettavat sisäpuhelimet hätätilanteita varten; Henkilökohtaiset turvahälyttimet; Sähköiset ovikellot; Varkaudenestovaroittimet; Silmälasinkehykset; Silmälasit [optiikka]; Silmälasikotelot; Matkapuhelinten akkujen laturit; Sähköparistot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Chronographes [appareils enregistreurs de durées]; Balances électroniques; Règles graduées; Clignotants [signaux lumineux]; Interphones; Instruments de localisation mondiale [GPS]; Casques d'écoute; Haut-parleurs sans fil; Télescopes; Bouées de sauvetage; Interphones d'urgence portatifs; Alarmes de sécurité personnelle; Sonnettes de portes, électriques; Avertisseurs contre le vol; Montures de lunettes; Lunettes [optique]; Étuis à lunettes; Chargeurs de batterie pour téléphones cellulaires; Piles électriques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kronografi [aparati za bilježenje trajanja]; Elektroničke vage; Ravnala za mjerenje; Treperujuća svjetla [svjetlosna signalizacija]; Portafoni; Instrumenti za globalno pozicioniranje; Slušalice; Bežični zvučnici; Teleskopi; Prsluci za spašavanje; Prenosivi interfoni za hitne slučajeve; Osobni sigurnosni alarmi; Električna zvonca za vrata; Signalni uredjaji protiv krađe; Okviri za naočale; Naočale [optika]; Etuiji za naočale; Punjači baterija mobitela; Električne baterije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kronográfok [időrögzítő készülékek]; Elektronikus mérlegek; Vonalzók; Villanófények, villogók; Kaputelefonok; Globális helymeghatározó eszközök; Fejhallgatók; Vezeték nélküli hangszórók; Teleszkópok; Mentőmellények; Hordozható vészhelyzeti távbeszélők; Személyi riasztók; Elektromos ajtócsengők; Betörésgátló riasztókészülékek; Szemüvegkeretek; Szemüvegek [optika]; Szemüvegtokok; Akkumulátortöltők mobiltelefonokhoz; Elektromos elemek, akkumulátorok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cronografi [apparecchi registratori di durata]; Bilance elettroniche; Stecche di misura da una iarda; Lampeggiatori [segnali luminosi]; Citofoni; Apparecchiature di posizionamento globale; Auricolari; Altoparlanti senza fili; Telescopi; Boe di salvataggio; Interfoni d'emergenza portatili; Allarmi per la sicurezza personale; Campanelli elettrici per porte; Avvisatori antifurto; Montature di occhiali; Occhiali [ottica]; Astucci per occhiali; Caricabatteria per telefoni cellulari; Batterie elettriche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Chronografai [laiko registravimo aparatai]; Elektroninės svarstyklės; Matavimo liniuotės; Blykstės lempos [šviesos signalai]; Vidinio ryšio įrenginiai; Globalinės padėties nustatymo prietaisai; Ausinės; Bevieliai garsiakalbiai; Teleskopai; Gelbėjimo liemenės; Nešiojamosios avarinės vidaus ryšio sistemos; Asmeniniai saugos signalizatoriai; Elektriniai durų skambučiai; Apsaugos nuo vagysčių signalizacijos; Akinių rėmai; Akiniai [optika]; Akinių dėklai; Mobiliojo ryšio telefonų baterijų įkrovikliai; Elektrinės baterijos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Hronogrāfi; Elektroniskie svari; Lineāli ar skalu; Mirgojošas signālierīces; Aprīkojums iekšējo telesakaru nodrošināšanai; Globālās vietnoteices ierīces; Ieaušu austiņas; Bezvadu skaļruņi; Teleskopi; Glābšanas vestes; Pārvietojami avārijas namruņi; Personiskās drošības sistēmas; Elektriskie durvju zvani; Pretielaušanās brīdinājuma sistēmas; Briļļu rāmji; Brilles; Briļļu maki; Mobilo tālruņu akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces; Elektriskie akumulatori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kronografi [tagħmir li jkejjel il-ħin]; Mwieżen elettroniċi; Rigi tal-kejl; Dwal indikaturi; Interkoms; Strumenti għas-sejbien tal-pożizzjoni fid-dinja; Kuffji; Spikers mingħajr fili; Teleskopji; Salvawomi; Interkoms tal-emerġenza li jistgħu jinġarru; Allarmi ta' sigurtà personali; Qniepen tal-bieb tal-elettriku; Apparat ta' twissija ta' serq; Frejms għan-nuċċalijiet; Nuċċalijiet [ottiċi]; Kontenituri tan-nuċċalijiet; Ċarġers tal-batteriji għat-telefowns ċellulari; Batteriji tal-elettriku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Chronografen [tijdsduur-registratieapparaten]; Elektronische weegschalen; Meetlatten; Knipperlichten [signaallichten]; Intercoms; GPS-instrumenten; Oortelefoons; Draadloze luidsprekers; Telescopen; Reddingsboeien; Draagbare noodintercoms; Alarminstallaties voor persoonlijke veiligheid; Deurbellen, elektrisch; Alarmtoestellen tegen diefstal; Brilmonturen; Brillen; Brillenkokers; Batterijladers voor mobiele telefoons; Elektrische batterijen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Chronografy [aparaty rejestrujące przebieg zjawiska w czasie]; Wagi elektroniczne; Linijki pomiarowe; Światła błyskowe [sygnały świetlne]; Interkomy; Urządzenia GPS; Słuchawki [douszne]; Głośniki bezprzewodowe; Teleskopy; Kamizelki ratunkowe; Przenośne interkomy awaryjne; Osobiste alarmy bezpieczeństwa; Elektryczne dzwonki do drzwi; Alarmy antywłamaniowe; Oprawki do okularów; Okulary [optyka]; Etui na okulary; Ładowarki do telefonów komórkowych; Baterie elektryczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cronógrafos [aparelhos de registo do tempo]; Balanças eletrónicas; Réguas de medição; Luzes intermitentes [sinais luminosos]; Intercomunicadores; Instrumentos de posicionamento global; Auriculares; Altifalantes (colunas de som) sem fios; Telescópios; Bóias de salvamento; Intercomunicadores de emergência portáteis; Alarmes de segurança pessoal; Campainhas de porta, elétricas; Aparelhos de alerta anti-roubo; Armações de óculos; Óculos [ótica]; Estojos para óculos; Carregadores de baterias de telemóveis; Baterias elétricas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cronografe [aparate de înregistrare a timpului]; Cântare electronice; Rigle de măsurare; Semnale luminoase intermitente; Interfoane; Aparate de poziţionare globală; Căşti auriculare; Boxe fara fir; Telescoape; Veste de salvare; Interfoane de urgenţă portabile; Alarme pentru siguranţă personală; Sonerii de uşă, electrice; Sisteme de alarmă antiefracţie; Rame de ochelari fără braţe; Ochelari [optică]; Tocuri pentru ochelari fără braţe; Încărcătoare de baterii pentru telefoane mobile; Baterii galvanice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Chronografy (prístroje na zaznamenávanie časových údajov); Elektronické váhy; Meracie pravítka; Blikavé svetlá (svetelné signály); Domový alebo palubný telefón; Globálne zariadenia na určenie polohy; Slúchadlá; Bezdrôtové reproduktory; Teleskopy; Záchranné bóje; Prenosné núdzové interkomy; Osobné bezpečnostné alarmy (poplachové zariadenia); Elektrické dverové zvončeky; Alarmy proti vlámaniu; Rámy na okuliare; Okuliare; Puzdrá na okuliare; Nabíjačky batérií pre mobilné telefóny; Elektrické batérie (články).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kronografi [aparati za beleženje časa]; Elektronske tehtnice; Ravnila za merjenje; Utripalke [signalne luči]; Interfoni; Instrumenti za globalno pozicioniranje; Slušalke; Brezžični zvočniki; Teleskopi; Rešilni jopiči; Prenosni interfoni za nujne primere; Osebni varnostni alarmi; Električni hišni zvonci; Protivlomni opozorilni aparati; Okvirji za očala; Očala [optika]; Etuiji za očala; Polnilniki za baterije, za mobilne telefone; Električne baterije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kronografer [tidregistreringsapparater]; Elektroniska vågar; Metermått för ingenjörer; Varningsljus [blinkande]; Snabbtelefoner; Globala positioneringsinstrument; Öronsnäckor; Högtalare för trådlös användning; Teleskop; Flytvästar; Bärbara snabbtelefoner för nödsituationer; Larm för personlig säkerhet; Elektriska dörrklockor; Inbrottsalarm; Glasögonbågar; Glasögon; Glasögonfodral; Batteriladdare till mobiltelefoner; Batterier, elektriska.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Купи за плодове; Стъклени купи; Стъклени халби; Чаши, направени от керамика; Керамика за домакински цели; Чайници; Бутилки за течности при спортуване; Сервизи за кафе, не от благороден метал; Градинарски лейки; Средства за почистване; Четки за зъби; Копринени конци за зъболекарски цели; Козметични четки; Термоси; Домашни аквариуми; Капани за мишки; Насекоми (Електрически уреди за привличане и унищожаване -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Misky na ovoce; Skleněné mísy; Skleněné hrnečky; Keramické hrnky; Keramika pro použití v domácnosti; Čajové konvice; Lahve na pití pro sportovní účely; Kávové servisy [stolní nádobí]; Konve na zalévání; Čisticí potřeby; Zubní kartáčky; Zubní nit; Štětce na nanášení líčidel; Izolované lahve; Interiérová akvária; Pasti na myši; Elektrická zařízení na vábení a hubení hmyzu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Frugtskåle; Glasbowler; Glaskrus; Krus af lertøj; Keramik til husholdningsbrug; Tepotter; Drikkedunke til brug ved sport; Kaffeservicer [bordservice]; Vandkander; Redskaber til rengøringsformål; Tandbørster; Tandtråd; Kosmetikbørster; Termoflasker; Akvarier til indendørs brug; Musefælder; Elektriske apparater til tiltrækning og udryddelse af insekter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche; Obstschalen; Glaskugeln; Tassen aus Glas; Steingut-Krüge; Keramikerzeugnisse für den Haushalt; Teekannen; Taschenflaschen; Kaffeeservice [Tafelgeschirr]; Gießkannen; Putzzeug; Zahnbürsten; Zahnseide; Kosmetikpinsel; Isolierflaschen; Zimmeraquarien; Fallen für Mäuse; Insektenanlock- und -vertilgungsgeräte, elektrische.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Φρουτιέρες· Γαβάθες γυάλινες· Γυάλινες κούπες· Φλιτζάνια από φαγεντιανά· Κεραμικά (Προϊόντα -) για οικιακή χρήση· Τσαγιέρες· Παγούρια για τον αθλητισμό· Σερβίτσια καφέ [επιτραπέζια σκεύη]· Ποτιστήρια· Είδη καθαρισμού· Βουρτσες (Οδοντό -)· Νήμα οδοντικό· Καλλυντικές βούρτσες· Φιάλες ισοθερμικές· Ενυδρεία εσωτερικού χώρου· Ποντικοπαγίδες· Ηλεκτρικές διατάξεις προσέλκυσης και εξόντωσης εντόμων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Containers for household or kitchen use; Fruit cups; Glass bowls; Glass mugs; Mugs made of earthenware; Ceramics for household purposes; Tea pots; Drinking bottles for sports; Coffee services [tableware]; Watering cans; Articles for cleaning purposes; Tooth brushes; Dental floss; Make-up brushes; Insulating flasks; Indoor aquaria; Mouse traps; Electric devices for attracting and killing insects.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Copas para fruta; Bolas de vidrio; Tazas de vidrio; Tazones de loza; Artículos de cerámica para uso doméstico; Teteras; Cantimploras; Servicios de café [vajilla]; Regaderas; Material de limpieza; Cepillos de dientes; Hilo dental; Cepillos para uso cosmético; Termos; Acuarios de interior; Ratoneras [trampas para ratones]; Insectos (Dispositivos eléctricos para atraer y eliminar -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Puuviljavaagnad; Klaaskausid; Klaaskruusid; Savikruusid; Keraamilised majatarbed, kodukeraamika; Teekannud; Sportimisel kasutatavad joogipudelid; Kohviserviisid [lauanõud]; Kastekannud; Puhastus- ja koristustarbed; Hambaharjad; Niit (Hamba -), hambaniit; Kosmeetikaharjad; Termospudelid; Toaakvaariumid; Hiirelõksud; Elektrilised vahendid putukate püüdmiseks ja tapmiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Hedelmäkulhot; Lasikulhot; Lasimukit; Keramiikasta tehdyt mukit; Keramiikka kotitaloustarkoituksiin; Teepannut; Taskumatit; Kahviastiastot; Kastelukannut; Puhdistukseen käytettävät tarvikkeet; Hammasharjat; Hammaslanka; Harjat kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Termospullot; Sisäakvaariot; Rotanloukut; Hyönteisten houkutus- ja hävityslaitteet [sähkökäyttöiset].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Coupes à fruits; Boules de verre; Chopes en verre; Tasses [mugs] en faïence; Céramique à usage domestique; Théières; Flasques de poche; Services à café; Arrosoirs; Matériel de nettoyage; Brosses à dents; Fil dentaire; Pinceaux de maquillage; Bouteilles isolantes; Aquariums d'appartement; Souricières; Dispositifs électriques pour attirer et détruire les insectes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Zdjele za voće; Staklene zdjele; Staklene šalice; Glinene šalice; Keramički proizvodi za kućanstvo; Čajnici; Sportske bočice za vodu [bidoni]; Servisi za kavu [stolno posuđe]; Kante za zalijevanje; Pribor za čišćenje; Četkice za zube; Konac za njegu zubi; Kozmetičke četke; Izolacijske boce; Kućni akvariji; Mišolovke; Električni uređaji za privlačenje i uništavanje insekata.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Kompótos tálka; Üvegtálak; Üveg csészék; Agyagbögrék; Kerámiák háztartási használatra; Teáskannák; Ivópalackok sportoláshoz; Kávéskészletek; Locsolókannák, öntözőkannák; Takarítóeszközök; Fogkefék; Fogselyem; Kozmetikai ecsetek, pipere ecsetek; Termoszok; Akváriumok (Szobai -); Egérfogók; Elektromos rovarcsapdák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Coppe da frutta; Bocce di vetro; Boccali di vetro; Tazze alte in terracotta; Prodotti di ceramica per uso domestico; Teiere; Bidoncini [fiaschette]; Servizi da caffè; Innaffiatoi; Articoli per la pulizia; Spazzolini da denti; Filo dentario; Pennelli per il trucco; Bottiglie isolanti; Acquari da appartamento; Trappole per topolini; Dispositivi elettrici per l'attrazione e distruzione degli insetti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Vaisių vazos; Stiklinės taurės; Stikliniai puodeliai; Moliniai puodeliai; Buitiniai keramikos dirbiniai; Arbatinukai; Sportininkų gertuvės; Kavos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys]; Laistytuvai; Valymo reikmenys; Dantų šepetukai; Tarpdančių valymo siūlai; Kosmetiniai šepetėliai; Termosai; Kambariniai akvariumai; Pelių spąstai; Elektriniai vabzdžių viliojimo ir naikinimo prietaisai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Augļu trauki; Stikla bļodas; Stikla krūkas; Krūzes, kas izgatavotas no keramikas; Keramikas izstrādājumi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Tējkannas; Dzērienu pudeles sportam; Kafijas servīzes [galda piederumi]; Lejkannas; Tīrīšanas un apkopšanas rīki un ierīces; Zobu sukas; Zobu diegi; Kosmētikas otiņas; Vakuuma pudeles; Istabas akvāriji; Peļu slazdi; Kukaiņu pievilināšanas un iznīcināšanas elektriskās ierīces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Tazzi tal-frott; Skutelli tal-ħġieġ; Maggijiet tal-ħġieġ; Kikkri magħmula mill-fuħħar; Ċeramika għal skopijiet domestiċi; Tettieri; Fliexken tax-xorb għall-isports; Servizzi tal-kafè [oġġetti tal-mejda]; Laned għat-tisqija; Oġġetti għat-tindif; Xkupilji tas-snien; Ħajt għal skopijiet ta' tindif dentali; Pniezel kożmetiċi; Termos; Akkwarji (ta' ġewwa); Nases għall-ġrieden; Apparat tal-elettriku biex jattira u joqtol l-insetti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Fruitschalen; Glazen bollen; Mokken van glas; Bekers vervaardigd uit aardewerk; Keramische gebruiksvoorwerpen, voor de huishouding; Theepotten; Heupflessen; Koffieserviezen; Gieters; Reinigingsmateriaal; Tandenborstels; Tandzijde; Borstels voor cosmetische doeleinden; Thermosflessen; Aquaria voor binnenshuis; Muizenvallen; Elektrische inrichtingen voor het aantrekken en doden van insecten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Pucharki na owoce; Miski ze szkła; Kubki szklane; Kubki gliniane; Wyroby ceramiczne dla gospodarstwa domowego; Czajniczki do herbaty; Butelki na napoje dla podróżnych; Serwisy do kawy [zastawa stołowa]; Konewki; Sprzęt do czyszczenia; Szczoteczki do zębów; Nici dentystyczne; Pędzle kosmetyczne; Termosy; Akwaria pokojowe; Pułapki na myszy; Owady [Elektryczne urządzenia do wabienia i zabijania -].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Taças para fruta; Tijelas em vidro; Canecas de vidro; Canecas de faiança; Cerâmicas para uso doméstico; Chaleiras [bules para chá]; Cantis para desportos; Serviços de café [louça de mesa]; Regadores; Material de limpeza; Escovas de dentes; Fio dental; Escovas para fins cosméticos; Garrafas térmicas; Aquários de interior; Ratoeiras para ratos; Dispositivos elétricos para atrair e eliminar insetos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Cupe pentru fructe; Boluri de sticlă; Căni din sticlă; Căni confecţionate din ceramică; Ceramice (produse - pentru menaj); Ceainice; Sticle pentru băuturi pentru sportivi; Servicii de cafea [veselă]; Stropitori; Material pentru curăţare; Periuţe de dinţi; Aţă dentară; Pensule de uz cosmetic; Termosuri; Acvarii de interior; Curse pentru şoareci; Dispozitive electrice pentru atragerea şi omorârea insectelor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Poháre na ovocie; Sklené gule; Sklené hrnčeky; Hrnčeky z keramiky (kameniny); Keramické výrobky pre domácnosť; Čajníky; Čutory, cestovné fľaše; Kávové súpravy (stolový riad); Polievacie kanvy; Prostriedky a pomôcky na čistenie; Zubné kefky; Dentálne nite; Kozmetické štetce; Termosky; Bytové akváriá; Myši (Pasce na -); Elektrické zariadenia na priťahovanie a ničenie hmyzu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Skodelice za sadje; Steklene sklede; Steklene skodelice; Lončeni skodelice; Keramični izdelki za gospodinjstvo; Čajniki; Plastenka za vodo za šport; Kavni servisi; Kangle za zalivanje; Čistilne priprave; Zobne ščetke; Zobna nitka; Čopiči za kozmetične namene; Termovke; Sobni akvariji; Mišolovke; Električne naprave, ki privlačijo in uničujejo mrčes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Bägare för frukt; Glasskålar; Glasmuggar; Muggar tillverkade av lergods; Keramik för hushållsändamål; Tekannor; Dryckesflaskor för sport; Kaffeserviser [bordsserviser]; Vattenkannor; Artiklar för rengöringsändamål; Tandborstar; Tandtråd för dentala ändamål; Sminkborstar; Termosflaskor; Inomhusakvarier; Musfällor; Elektriska anordningar för att dra åt sig och döda insekter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/075</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/144</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-31</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1057486</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15066</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
